特洛伊。特洛伊,你准备好了吗?你的游戏完成了吗?
Troy. Troy, you ready? Is your game done?
我已经开始了一个新的。
I already started a new one.
一个新的吗?
A new one?
老兄，我还没玩完你最后一款游戏呢。
Dude, I haven't even finished playing your last game yet.
让我们把游戏放到应用商店里，好吗?
Look, let's put the games on the app store, right?
我会制作宣传视频。我们会发财。
I'll make the promo videos. We'll get rich.
然后女孩?嗯?
And then girls? Huh?
——嘿,女士们!——不。
- Hey, ladies! - Nope.
尼克，你知道这和女孩无关。
Nick, you know it's not about the girls, man.
而是关于创造一款优秀的游戏并在Pixelcon上展示它。
It's about making one great game and showing it off at Pixelcon.
是的,喜欢……就像你爸爸那样。
Yeah, like... like your dad did.
好吧，好吧。
All right, fine, fine.
至少让我看看我的Nickalicious频道吧?
Let me at least show my Nickalicious channel?
我是说，五分钱党肯定会喜欢的。
I mean, look, the Nickheads would love it.
我以为他们是五分钱影院?
I thought they were the Nickelodeons?
是的，版权问题，所以…
Yeah, copyright problems, so...
我们还在努力。
We're still workshopping it.
拜托，让我给他们看看?
Please, let me show them?
好吧。
Okay.
——真的吗?——没有。
- Really? - No.
至少让我妈妈看看吧?
Can I at least show my mom?
我来这里玩
♪ I came here to play ♪
< span style = " font - family: arial; font - family: arial; font - family: arial
♪ Gonna give them What they want ♪
>我来这里是为了玩
♪ Well I came here to play ♪
♬让他们等了这么长时间♬
♪ Kept them waiting For so long ♪
>别挡道
♪ Don't get in the way ♪
♬让你认为你认为你已经看到了所有的东西
♪ Makes you think you think You've seen it all ♪
>我来这里是为了玩
♪ Well I came here to play ♪
i 'm slingin' fire
♪ I'm slingin' fire ♪
♬From my指尖♬
♪ From my fingertips ♪
♪ Oh here we go ♪
♬我在出界，你能处理这个吗?♪我> < /
♪ I'm dishing out Can you handle this? ♪
我靠我自己
♪ I'm on my own ♪
♪ Oh oh oh oh oh ♪
yes yes♬
♪ Yeah yeah ♪
♪ Oh here we go ♪
>我在路上
♪ I'm on the road ♪
>我来这里是为了玩
♪ Well I came here to play ♪
< span style = " font - family: arial; font - family: arial; font - family: arial
♪ Gonna give them What they want ♪
>我来这里是为了玩
♪ Well I came here to play ♪
♬让他们等了这么长时间♬
♪ Kept them waiting For so long ♪
>别挡道
♪ Don't get in the way ♪
我的名字叫Troy Mayfield
My name's Troy Mayfield.
> i love making video games. >我喜欢制作视频游戏
I love making video games.
>
I always have.
我妈妈和爸爸开了一家游戏公司
My mom and dad started a gaming company
when i was little.
when I was little.
i> . i> . i> . i> . i> . i> . i> . i>
All I've ever wanted to do is work there.
但是因为某些原因，我妈妈认为我还没有准备好
But for some reason my mom doesn't think I'm ready.
So, for now, i 'm stuck in Mr. Diehl's . So, for now, i 'm stuck in Mr. Diehl's . So, for now, i 'm stuck in Mr. Diehl's
So, for now, I'm stuck in Mr. Diehl's
十年级计算机科学班，
tenth grade computer science class,
编码…这个。
coding... this.
好的,十分钟。十分钟!
Okay, ten minutes. Ten minutes!
这是我发现的时刻
It's the moment I find out
我是不是一个好老师。
if I'm a good teacher or not.
伙计，我们需要你的帮助!
Dude, we need your help!
他们在最黑暗的时刻寻求他的帮助……
They come to him for help in their darkest hour...
你知道发生了什么吗?
Do you have any idea what's going on?
来吧,特洛伊。
Come on, Troy.
这对我们来说没有任何意义。
This doesn't make any sense to us.
我记得你们说过想自己做。
I thought you guys said you wanted to do it on your own.
- - -完成。-我想我把它弄坏了。
- And done. - I think I broke it.
我们需要你的帮助，特洛伊。
We need your help, Troy.
这是你成绩的一半。
This is worth half your grade.
五分钟!
Five minutes!
那不是五分钟。
That was not five minutes.
开心的时候时间过得很快。
Time flies when you're having fun.
两分钟!
Two minutes!
什么……
What...
A或者f，这就是你的答案。
A or F. That's what you're gonna get.
我决定这么做是因为我很疯狂。
I just decided that because I'm crazy AF.
五个
Five...
四个……
four...
三个……
three...
两个……
two...
一个!
one!
你是一个天才。你应该在EA或者Xodus工作。
You're a genius. You should work at EA or Xodus.
Xodus糟透了。
Xodus sucks.
抱歉打扰了，但我得和特洛伊谈谈。
I'm sorry to interrupt but I need to talk to Troy.
合十礼,每一个人。
Namaste, everyone.
合十礼，古德森副校长。
Uh, namaste, Vice Principal Goodson.
合十礼。
Namaste.
合十礼吗?
Namaste?
很好，很好。
That's good, that's good.
再嘲笑我吧
Laugh at me again
我会带你们每个人去遛狗
and I will dog walk every one of you!
一切都好吗?
Is everything okay?
辛西娅离开我了。
Cynthia left me.
——不!-是的。
- No! - Yeah.
嗯……特洛伊?
Umm... Troy?
德、德。来吧。
Mayfield, Mayfield. Come on.
我稍后再打给你。
I'll call you later.
请。
Please.
威廉姆斯，别再拍人了。
Uh, Williams, stop filming people.
这不是真人秀，好吗?
This isn't a reality show, okay?
特洛伊……我意识到一件非常严重的事情
Troy... I have become aware of a very serious matter
我想让你给我解释一下
and I want you to try to explain it to me.
♬她把我缠在她的手指上
♪ She's got me wrapped Around her finger ♪
从来没见过更清晰的♬
♪ Never seen it clearer ♪
嘿,特洛伊!
Hey, Troy!
我真的能闻到荷尔蒙的味道
I can honestly smell the hormones
从你嘴里吐出来，真恶心。
pouring out of you, and it's nauseating.
根据这份报告…
And according to this report...
我们的80个学生
all 80 of our students
在考试中得了满分
got a perfect score on a test
是你辅导他们的。
that you helped tutor them for.
突出。
Outstanding.
就这样我们赢得了全国一等奖……
And that's how we won the nationwide first prize...
新电脑!哈哈哈!
New computers! Hahaha!
哇。
Wow.
我一直在求主管
I've been begging the superintendent
用了六年的空调，
for air conditioning for about six years,
但是新电脑是好的。
but new computers are good.
古德森先生,恭喜你。
Congratulations, Mr. Goodson.
八十年完美的分数。
Eighty perfect scores.
学校真的很需要这些电脑。
The school really needed these computers.
-对，对，对。-但问题是
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - But the problem is
我们只有15名学生参加了比赛。
is that only 15 of our students entered the competition.
这是奇怪的……你会检查的。
That is odd... that you would check that.
是啊!天啊，我有个问题要问你
Yeah! Oh my god, I had a question for you
我不得不把它写下来
and I had to write it down
因为我并不完全理解它。
because I don't really fully understand it.
我老了，你知道吗?
I'm old, you know?
你非法黑进国家科学基金会的数据库了吗
Did you illegally hack into the NSF database
操纵标准化测试结果?
and manipulate standardized testing results?
我只是想帮助学校。
I was only trying to help the school.
和你……因为这是…
And you have... 'cause this is...
我的!哈哈哈。
Mine! Hahahaha.
我是说，如果有没有受害者的犯罪。
I mean, if there ever was a victimless crime.
不过我得把你停职了。
I do have to suspend you though.
我只是今晚不需要这个，好吗?
I just did not need this tonight, okay?
你知道今晚对操场游戏有多重要。
You know how important tonight is for Playfield Games.
实际上,我不喜欢。
Actually, I don't.
你还没告诉我今晚是怎么回事。
You never told me what tonight's all about.
妈妈，现在我有空闲时间了，
You know, Mom, now that I have some free time,
我可以来上班。
I could come to work.
我可以去公司帮忙…
I could come help out at the company...
不，你不会得到奖赏的
No, you're not gonna get rewarded
因为被停职了，好吗?
for getting suspended, all right?
哦!我有一个完美的方法
Oh! I've got the perfect way
一个被停学的学生今晚可以帮忙。
a suspended student can help out tonight.
This is a fair punishment.这是公平的惩罚
This is a fair punishment.
>我想知道我是否可以把这个办公室聚会改为
I wonder if I could turn this office party
进入某种电子游戏?
into some kind of video game?
但是我应该扮演哪个角色?
But which character would I play as?
林登!东西用金钱…
Lyndon! Something with money...
Or i guess i could play as
Or I guess I could play as...
劳拉!技术领导，我认为
Laura! Technical lead, I think...
或玛丽!嗯…总是好。
Or Marie! Uh... always been nice.
玩我妈妈太奇怪…
Playing as my mom would be too weird...
凯特!CEO。
Kate! CEO.
但我会有一根很酷的手杖作为武器。
But I would have a pretty cool cane as a weapon.
然后是……
And then there's...
特洛伊，他来了。
Troy the boy, there he is.
吉米!首席设计师…
Jimmy! Lead designer...
不，不，不，不是他!绝对不是他!
no, no, no, not him! Definitely not him!
返回，control Z, control Z!
Go back, control Z, control Z!
在现实生活中行不通
That doesn't work in real life.
告诉我，特洛伊·贝哈尔，发生了什么?
Go ahead and tell me Troy Behar, what's going on?
我听说你今天被学校开除了。
I heard you got kicked out of school today.
如果你想找点事做，
Well, if you're looking for something to do,
我们可以让你去游乐场工作。
we could probably put you to work over at Playfield.
等待,真的吗?那真是太棒了。
Wait, really? That actually would be awesome.
是的。你知道怎么擦吗?
Yeah. Do you know how to squeegee?
呵呵。只是kiddin”。
Hehe. Just kiddin'.
吉米!布鲁斯在这里。来吧。
Jimmy! Bruce is here. Come on.
是的。
Yeah.
嘿!
Hey!
好吧,呃,嗨。
Well, uh, hi.
我知道你。我看到你。
I know you. I-I saw you.
是的,在学校。
Yeah, at school.
是你，对吧?今天……唱歌吗?
That was you, right? Today... singing?
是啊，我刚搬去和我爷爷林登一起住。
Yeah, I just moved in with my grandpa, Lyndon.
他想让我出去社交。
He wanted me to get out and socialize.
你是第一个80岁以下的人
You're actually like the first person under 80
我在学校外认识的人。
I've met outside of school.
相同。
Same.
嗯…好吧。
Uh... okay.
-那个dj是你朋友吗?-一，二，三，啊!
- So is that deejay your friend? - One, two, three, ah!
一，二，三，啊!一，二，三，啊!
One, two, three, ah! One, two, three, ah!
是的,尼克。
Yeah, Nick.
他是我最好的朋友。
Well, he's my best friend.
其实是我唯一的朋友。
My only friend, actually.
是的…但他很了不起。
Yeah... but he is a lot.
所以…特洛伊，是吗?
So... Troy the boy, is it?
啊…特洛伊。
Ah... just Troy.
佩奇。
Just Paige.
对不起,嗯…
Sorry, um...
你是第一个真正理解我们的天使投资人。
So, you are the first angel investor who really gets us.
事情的真相是
The truth of the matter is
我的孙子们一直在追我
my grandkids have been after me
投资一些很酷的东西，你知道的，永远的。
to invest into something cool, you know, forever.
我对比特币非常感兴趣。
And, well, I am very deep into BitCoin.
——哇。——是的!
- Whoa. - Yeah!
但我们之间，我真的不知道那是什么。
But between us, I don't really know what it is.
不，没人知道。
No, no one does.
他们沉迷于你以前的游戏。
And they are obsessed with your old games.
所以我觉得这是十拿九稳的。
And so I just figured this was a shoo-in.
这是十拿九稳的，
It is a shoo-in,
你投资我们真是太聪明了。
and you're so smart to invest in us.
我们真的很感激你的加入。
And we're really grateful to have you onboard.
这对我们来说非常令人兴奋。
This is very exciting for us.
如果你想做点什么
If you want something to do,
那里有个卡拉ok机
there's, like, a karaoke machine
连接到扬声器…
hooked up to the speakers...
我真的不想成为焦点。
I'm really not looking for the spotlight.
是的。是的,完全。那很酷。
Yeah. Yeah, totally. That's cool.
这整件事到底是为了什么?
What's this whole thing for, anyway?
嗯…是给我妈妈的公司买的。
Uh... it's for my mom's company.
是的。我觉得这有很大的关系。
Yeah. I think there's a lot riding on it.
这是非常酷的。
It's very cool.
非常非常酷。
Very, very cool.
那是你爸爸吗?
Is that your dad?
不，我爸在我很小的时候就去世了。
No, my dad died when I was little.
我…我真的很抱歉。我不知道。
I'm... I'm really sorry. I didn't know.
不，完全没问题。那是很久以前的事了。
No, it's totally fine. It was a long time ago.
只有我和我妈
It's been just me and my mom
基本上我的整个人生，所以…
for like basically my whole life, so...
我能理解这一点。
I can kinda relate to that.
我爸也不在我生活中。
My dad's not really in my life either.
布鲁斯,在这里。现在仍然是beta。
Bruce, here. Now it's still in beta.
不要给别人看
Don't show it to anyone else,
但要把它放在孩子的枕头下。
but put it under your kids' pillows.
他们一定会很喜欢这个游戏的
They're gonna love this game so much
他们会尿床的!
they're gonna be wetting your bed!
Uhhhh……
Uhhhh...
事实上，我的孙子们确实有尿床的问题。
Actually, my grandkids do have a problem with wetting.
——所以……——啊……
- So... - Ahhh...
这有点问题。
It's a bit of a problem.
它是一个表达式。呵。
It's an expression. Heh-heh.
这是一个烂摊子。
It's a mess.
不，我喜欢你的想法。
But, no, I like where your head is.
好吧，我能先给你拿杯喝的吗?
Well, look, can I get you a drink before we ink?
非常非常好，我喜欢这个口号。
Very very good, I like that slogan.
知道吗，我很好，谢谢。
You know what, I'm good, thank you.
我要自己去拿，也就是说我会…
I'm gonna grab it myself, which means I will...
马上回来。
BRB.
这是我孙子教我的。
My grandkids taught me that.
哦,是的,是的。
Oh yes, yes.
上帝保佑他们。
God bless 'em.
好吧,哈哈。呵。
Well, LOL. Heh-heh.
我觉得那很脏。
I think that's dirty.
——不!不,不,不。——不,不。
- No! No, no, no. - No, no.
放声大笑或在线大笑。
Laugh out loud or laugh online.
不是每个人的笑。
Not everyone's laughing.
我们只是想找点乐子。呵呵呵。我们有一个很好的时间。
We just like to have fun. Heh heh. We have a good time.
天啊，你做了什么?
Oh my god, what did you do?
-我不知道我为什么说…-你为什么给他那个?
- I don't know why I said... - Why did you give him that?
-他会喜欢的——不,不。这不是准备好了!
- He's gonna love it. - No, no. It's not ready!
他不知道该拿它怎么办。
He won't know what to do with it.
-还没准备好。-你在开玩笑吗?这是准备好了。
- It's really not ready. - Are you kidding? It's ready.
他能看到一些小东西和机器人。
He'll be able to see little bits and bots.
它会没事的。
It'll be fine.
我能问你点事吗?
Hey, can I ask you something?
是的。
Yes.
她为什么需要那根拐杖?
Why does she need that cane?
她是一个向导。
She's a wizard.
一个向导吗?
A wizard?
她有一个…一个向导的城堡。
She has like a... a wizard castle.
拜托，拐杖是干什么用的?
Come on, what's the cane for?
嗯…她得了多发性硬化症。
Uh... well, she has MS.
我是二换二。
I'm two for two.
不,你很好。
No, you're fine.
这并不能让她慢下来。
It doesn't slow her down much.
似乎没有。
It doesn't seem to.
至少今晚不行。
At least not tonight.
嗬嗬，特洛伊的海伦!
Ho-ho, Helen of Troy!
啊!
Ah!
看来你不需要任何帮助
Looks like you don't need any help
去接一位女士。
picking up one of the ladies.
只是开玩笑。
Just kidding.
特洛伊·斯托里，你妈妈要开口了
Troy Story, your mom is about to start talking
所以如果你能处理好音乐
so if you can take care of the music
不管这是什么…不是。
and wrap up whatever this... isn't.
吉米……
Jimmy...
那家伙太棒了。
That guy is awesome.
是的，他是这么认为的。
Yeah, he thinks so.
——嗯。-恩……
- Ummm. - Ummmm...
是的,所以……好吧，我必须…
Yeah, so that... well, I do have to...
我得走了。
I have to go.
哦,是的,嗯…
Oh, yeah, uh...
嗯…再见……
Uh... see ya...
——再见。——再见。
- Bye. - Bye.
这东西很重。
This thing is heavy.
你的思想很强大，但你的手臂很虚弱。
Your mind is strong, but your arms are weak.
嘿,伙计们!
Hey, guys!
天啊，抱歉。
Oh, god, uh, sorry.
伟大的播放音乐。
Great deejaying.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
这只是我的副业。
It's just my side gig.
我更有影响力。
I'm more of an influencer.
我刚在YouTube上获得了上千个订阅。
I just crossed a thousand subs on YouTube.
你得去看看。
You gotta check it out.
是YouTube。com和Nickalicious。
It's YouTube dot com slash Nickalicious.
哦,对不起。我很抱歉。
Oh, excuse me. I'm sorry.
你们是千禧一代吗?
Are you millennials, by any chance?
我在这个东西上有个新游戏。
I have this new game on this thing here.
无论如何，它甚至还没有向公众开放，
Anyway, it's not even available to the public yet,
但我不知道该怎么下载。
but I'm just not sure how to download it.
你能帮我吗?
Could you help me?
我们到他的办公室去吧。
Let's step into his office.
粉碎,粉碎,粉碎。
Smashing, smashing, smashing.
看看这些剪报。
Look at all this clipping.
那家伙的头探出了大楼
The guy's head pokes out of the building
每次他都跳。
every time he jumps.
我打赌这东西的漏洞报告
I bet the bug report for this thing
大概有一英里长。
is like a mile long.
这配乐让我很难过。
This soundtrack makes me sad.
它只是为了复古而复古。
It just feels retro for retro's sake.
先生，你在哪儿找到的?
Sir, where'd you find this?
老兄，我随时都能让游戏出故障，看好了。
Dude, I can make the game glitch anytime I want, watch.
告诉丫。
Told ya.
先生，这只是我的意见，但别玩了
Sir, it's just my opinion, but throw this game out
去Playfield买个游戏
and get yourself a game from Playfield.
我几乎做到了。你留着吧。
I almost did. You can keep that.
哦,嘘…
Oh, shhhh...
这对我们所有人来说都是一个历史性的时刻。
This is kind of a historic moment for all of us.
因为我们终于找到了我们的天使投资人。
Because we have finally found our angel investor.
时机也不早，对吧，林登?
And not a moment too soon, right, Lyndon?
哇……唷!
Whoa... Whew!
好了，我想让大家举起酒杯。
Alright, I'd like everyone to raise your glasses.
废话少说，我给你布鲁斯!
Without any further ado, I give you Bruce!
布鲁斯，你在吗?来加入我们!
Bruce, are you here? Come join us!
他走了。
He's gone.
什么?
What?
从后面溜出去的，我不知道。
Slipped out the back, I don't know.
妈妈……
Mom...
特洛伊?
Troy?
哦……
Oh...
对不起，各位，我想我说得太早了，但是…
I'm sorry, everybody, I think I spoke too soon, but...
我很抱歉。
I'm sorry.
嘿,妈妈。
Hey, Mom.
嗯……妈妈，我很抱歉。
Umm... Mom, I'm so sorry.
我相信这对你来说一定很困难
I'm sure it must have been very difficult for you
不要破坏我们的游戏
to not rip apart our game
在派对上你唯一不认识的人面前。
in front of the only person you didn't know at the party.
我得想点别的办法。
I'm going to have to figure something else out.
凯特，这有点尴尬，但是…
Kate, this is awkward, but...
我们没有钱了。
we don't have any more money.
什么?
What?
我说了我们没钱了。
I said we have no more money.
但这是…这是银行，拉里。
But this is... this is a bank, Larry.
我们跑了出去。我叫人来。
We ran out. Let me call somebody.
因为我们是朋友。
Because we're friends.
好吧。
Okay.
嗨,杰夫。嗨。
Hey, Jeff. Hi.
是的,凯特在这里。好吧。
Yeah, Kate's here. Okay.
她拿不到钱?
She can't have the money?
因为我们没有更多了?
Because we don't have any more?
好吧，这就是我的想法。谢谢你！
Alright, that's what I thought. Thank you.
看到了吗?
See?
如果你不想把钱给我，
You know, if you don't want to give me the money,
你可以直接拒绝。
you could just say no.
不。
No.
你的工资单还在，我们不能。
With your payroll where it's at, we can't.
我是说，就算我们能，也不能。
I mean, even if we could, we can't.
我得走了…
You know what, I gotta go...
凯特,告诉我,
Kate, tell me,
什么风把你吹来了?
to what do I owe this pleasure?
我会直入正题的。
I'll cut straight to the chase.
我们遇到了一些困难，如果我们的游戏没有大获成功，
We've run into a bit of a snag and if our game isn't a big hit,
我们会有大麻烦的。
we're gonna be in a lot of trouble.
我想知道你是否有兴趣…
So, I was wondering if you might possibly be interested in...
买下你的游戏。我愿意为你这么做。
Buying out your games. Yeah, I would do that for you.
听着，凯特，在大学里玩你早期的游戏
Look, Kate, playing your early games in college
是我开始从事这一行的原因。
is what got me into this business to begin with.
我不知道"老里克"
You know, I don't know if "ol' Rickers"
在布朗大学待了五年半
would made it through five and a half years at Brown
如果不是Playfield Games
if it wasn't for Playfield Games.
我可能会去找女孩和毒品，
I probably would have just resorted to girls and drugs,
感谢上帝，你救了我。
so, thank God, you saved me from that.
哇。
Wow.
这是文件。我们会成功的。
So, here's the paperwork. We are gonna make this happen.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
呃，我有点奇怪
Uh, I'm a little weirded out
你都准备好了。
that you had this all prepared already.
我是一名童子军，凯特。我总是准备好了。
Well, I'm a Boy Scout, Kate. I'm always prepared.
好吧。太好了。
Okay. Great.
你知道吗…说话的男孩……
You know what, um... speaking of boys...
什么?
What?
嘿。你何不试试我们最新的游戏?
Hey. Why don't you take our latest game?
我肯定坦普尔曼会喜欢的。
I'm sure that Templeton's gonna love it.
临时…特洛伊?
Temp... Troy?
该死，我就知道是T开头的。
Dang it, I knew it started with a T.
你知道吗，反正我也要跟自己击掌
You know what, I'm gonna give myself a high five anyway
因为我已经很接近那个了。
because I got pretty close on that one.
好了，往高处走，宝贝!
Alright, up high, baby!
繁荣。
Boom.
另外，这里不会有工作机会
P.S. There would not be jobs here
当然是为了你的员工。
for any of your employees, of course.
很高兴见到你。
It's great to see you.
妈妈，我还没来得及告诉你你就走了
Mom, you left before I could tell you
但看看我对杰克豪斯做了什么。
but look what I did on Jackhouse.
哇，你真的进步很大。
Wow, you really did make a lot of progress.
看看这个。
Check this out.
Xodus吗?
Xodus?
(我得考虑把公司卖给他们。)
I have to consider selling the company to them.
什么?为什么?
What? Why?
这就是他们在Pixelcon发布的内容。
That's what they're releasing at Pixelcon.
>欢迎来到地狱星球
Welcome to Planet Hell.
准备输入您的信用卡信息
Prepare to enter your credit card information.
交易吗?这是可怕的。
Microtransactions? That's terrible.
什么……妈，这就像是高档的宰…
What the... Mom, this is like a high end rip-off of...
是的,那是……他们就是这么做的。
Yeah, that's... that's what they do.
妈妈，我不知道游乐场的情况这么糟。
Mom, I didn't know it was that bad at Playfield.
让我来帮你。
Let me come and help.
其实我很擅长这个。
I'm actually really good at this.
你和你爸爸拥有相同的天赋。
You and your dad share the same gift.
但他没有一个正常的童年
But he did not have a normal childhood
我们都发誓过你会的。
and we both swore to each other that you would.
我知道,妈妈……但是爸爸已经走了。
I know, Mom... but Dad is gone.
而且他已经很久了。
And he has been for a long time.
和…现在情况不太正常。
And... things aren't normal now.
我不知道你是怎么把这些加到游戏里的。
I don't know how you added all this to the game.
请……妈妈。
Please... Mom.
求你了，我觉得这是唯一的办法
Please, I feel like this is the only way
我可以弥补我所做的。
I can make up for what I did.
粉碎,粉碎,粉碎。
Smashing, smashing, smashing.
来吧，穿好衣服。我们要工作了。
Come on, get dressed. We're going to work.
嗨,劳拉,玛丽。
Hi, Laura, Marie.
我只想说我很抱歉
I just want to say I'm sorry
昨晚关于投资者的事。
about the investor thing last night.
你为投资者的事感到抱歉吗?
You're sorry about the investor thing?
你知道你做了什么吗?
Do you even understand what you did?
让我用你能理解的语言解释一下。
Let me explain it in words that you'll understand.
你做的事很不光彩，兄弟。
What you did was very, very not lit, fam.
别介意她，她只是太咸了
Don't mind her, she's just salty
因为你可能让我们丢了工作。
because you might've cost us all of our jobs.
扎克和科迪!
Zack and Cody!
嗨,吉米。
Hey, Jimmy.
嘿,猫猫。
Hey, slugger.
昨晚很漂亮的女孩。你参加比赛了吗?
Pretty girl last night. Did you get in the game?
去打棒球?
Get in the batter's box?
教练给你的信号?
Coach give you the signals?
不。不过我确实和杰克豪斯玩过。
No. I-I did play around with Jackhouse, though.
你怎么想?
What'd you think?
你真的想知道吗?
Uh, you really want to know?
是啊!
Yeah!
嗯,很好。
Uh, it's good.
这是好吗?就这些吗?
It was good? That's it?
哦,真的好吗?
Uh, really good?
真的好吗?这是伟大的!
Really good? It is great!
这是我的马里奥3。这是一场完美的比赛。
This is my Mario 3. This is a perfect game.
你知道吗，那个老头，他就是不明白。
You know what, that old man, he just didn't get it.
叫杰克豪斯是因为他们用电钻钻房子?
And it's Jackhouse because they jackhammer houses?
是啊!看吧，你懂的。
Yeah! See, you get it.
杰克豪斯是因为手提钻，对吧?
Jackhouse because of the jackhammer, right?
她得到它。这里的每个人都懂。
She gets it. Everyone here gets it.
它是可以获得的。
It is gettable.
我们要造出这个东西，让它摇滚起来。
We're gonna build this thing and it's going to rock.
好吧?你妈妈会找到现金的
All right? Your mom is gonna find cash
去别的地方吧。
somewhere else for it.
但是，我们会没事的。
But, we're gonna be okay.
凯特，我不想做常客
Kate, I-I hate to be such a regular
沮丧的黛比，
Debbie Down in the Dumps,
但我们确实需要管理我们的现金流状况。
but we-we do need to manage our cash flow situation.
我知道，我知道。我有个计划。
I know, I know. And I have a plan.
我是说，如果我们不撞到他们的袜子
I mean, if we don't knock their socks
从水里出来的时候，
right out of the water at that show,
我们……我们下个月不发工资了。
we... we won't make payroll next month.
还有另一种解决办法。呃……
There is another solution. The uh...
不。
No.
凯特，凯特，听着，裁员是现实。
Kate, Kate, look, uh, layoffs are a fact of life.
我不能违背我和乔治的承诺
I can't break the promise that George and I made
12年前的事了。
12 years ago to all of you.
我们得想个更好的办法。
We'll just have to find a better way.
我知道我们会的，凯特。
Oh, I know we will, Kate.
我知道我们会的。
I know we will.
我们总是这样做。
We always do.
人们会明白的。他们理解。
People will get it. They understand.
好吧?这很有趣。可玩。
All right? It's fun. It's playable.
我需要你…我想让你看看。
I need you... I want you to see it.
你看到了吗?你看到我了吗?
Do you see it? Do you see me?
你看到了吗?你看不出来吗?
Do you see it? You don't see it?
这是一个赢家。
It's a winner.
这就是我要说的。
That's all I'm saying.
赢家!
Winner!
所以…吉米，劳拉，所有人
So... Jimmy, Laura, everyone out there
花了几周的时间来解决这些小问题吗
has been working weeks to try and fix those glitches
你一个晚上就搞定了。
that you managed to fix in one night.
你添加的所有新功能…
And all those new features you added...
是合法的。
Are legit.
他们太合法了。
They are too legit.
是的。哦!等等!
Yeah. Oh! Wait!
不,妈妈,不要……
No, Mom, don't...
♬太合法而不能放弃
♪ Too legit to quitttttt ♪
是的。还有它。
Yeah. Still got it.
不开玩笑了，我们需要重新审视一下。
Look, all joking aside, we need a fresh look at things.
碰巧我们的团队…
And it just so happens that our team is...
粉碎。
Smashing.
刚出主意的
...fresh out of ideas.
所以我让你负责杰克豪斯。
That's why I am putting you in charge of Jackhouse.
你是在耍我还是…?
Are you messing with me or...?
不，你最好别让我后悔。
No, and you better not make me regret this.
你只需要在这个游戏上帮我们
You're just going to help us with this one game
然后和你一起回学校。
and then it's back to school with you.
哇，等等，我的天。
Wow, wait, holy crap.
所以，我要负责比赛了。
So, I get to be in charge of the game.
等等，吉米也是我管的吗?
Wait, am I in charge of Jimmy too?
你疯了吗?
Are you out of your mind?
你只要看看他昨晚做了什么，好吗?
You just have to see what he did last night, okay?
他修复了所有的bug
He fixed all of the bugs
他创造了所有这些可定制的皮肤。
and he created all these customizable skins.
有一道彩虹会说话
There's a rainbow that talks,
还有巴拉克·奥巴马，还有，还有水母。
there's Barack Obama, there's, there's a jellyfish.
这是疯了!我要疯了。
This is insane! I'm going insane.
我知道你很努力，
Look, I know how hard you've worked,
但是我们没有时间了。
but we are out of time.
所以，你要把这个拇指吸盘
So, you're gonna put this thumbsucker
负责我的游戏?
in charge of my game?
——嘿!——吉米!
- Hey! - Jimmy!
在Pixelcon之前，Troy负责所有的游戏决策。
Troy is in charge of all game decisions until Pixelcon.
结束讨论。
End of discussion.
现在我们开始工作吧。
Now let's get to work.
特洛伊，我想让你在你爸以前的办公室里办公。
Troy, I'd like you to set up in your dad's old office.
好吧。
Okay.
来吧。
Come on.
对不起,吉米。这是必须的。
I'm sorry, Jimmy. This is the way it has to be.
你妈妈让你留着手机吗?
Your mom let you keep your phone?
老兄,那就更好了。
Dude, even better.
我会告诉你一切的
I will tell you all about it
如果你放学后带几只红牛来操场的话
if you bring a few Red Bulls to Playfield after school.
哇,哇,哇。你是说操场吗?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Did you say Playfield?
- 哇，哇，哇… -红牛。好吧,再见!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa... - Red Bulls. Okay, bye!
你觉得呢?♪我> < /
♪ What do you say? ♪
♬你想玩吗?♪我> < /
♪ Do you want to play? ♪
你觉得呢?♪我> < /
♪ What do you say? ♪
♬你是游戏吗?♪我> < /
♪ Are you game? ♪
♬你是游戏游戏游戏游戏游戏游戏你是游戏吗?♪我> < /
♪ Are you game game game Game game are you game? ♪
你觉得呢?♪我> < /
♪ What do you say? ♪
♬你想玩吗?♪我> < /
♪ Do you want to play? ♪
哇。
Wow.
佩吉，你在这干嘛?
Paige, what are you doing here?
我现在和爷爷住在一起
I'm staying with my grandpa right now
等我父母"解决问题"
while my parents "work things out."
所以，我每天放学后都要来这里。
So, I have to come here every day after school.
哦。听到这个消息我很难过。
Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
我的意思是……对你的父母。
I mean... about your parents.
你能来这里真是太好了。
It's great that you get to be here.
我也得待在这里。
I have to be here too.
这是谁的办公室?
Whose office is this?
这是我爸爸以前的办公室，或者说曾经是，
It's my dad's old office, or it used to be,
但现在是我的了。
but it's actually mine now.
是啊，我妈让我负责比赛。
Yeah, my mom put me in charge of the game.
她什么?
She what?
我的天啊!
Holy crap and a half!
这是真的。
This is really happening.
-是的，哦，是的。-这是真的!
- Yes, oh, yes. - This is really happening!
哦!哦!哦!哦!哦!哦!哦!哦!哦!
Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh! Ohh!
是的,哇!是的,是的!
Yeah, whoo! Yes, yes!
心理!喔!
Psych! Ohhhh!
你们有没有想过
Hey, have you guys ever thought of
也许像某人在看《i>》那样跳舞?
maybe dancing like somebody is watching?
这是你的命运。
This is your destiny.
——容易,兄弟。-我有作业要做。
- Easy, bro. - I've got homework to do.
你们俩可以讨论你们的命运，但是，
You two can discuss your destiny, but, um,
我想以后再听你说。
I want to hear about this later.
肯定的。
For sure.
越来越好了。
This is getting better and better.
-这是最好的。——团队…
- It's the best. - Team...
特洛伊,会议室!
Troy, conference room!
——是的!-伙计…
- Yes! - Dude...
是时候和我的团队开第一次会了。
It's time for my first meeting with the team.
我该怎么办?
What do I do?
我不知道。就说他们想听的吧。
I don't know. Just tell them what they want to hear.
好的建议。
Good advice.
这是个好建议。
It is good advice.
给他们下地狱。
Give 'em hell.
嘿，我可以当实习生吗?
Hey, can I be an intern?
薪水是多少?
What's the pay like?
好吧，我不在乎。
Well, I don't care.
就是无薪实习!
Unpaid intern it is!
让我把它清理一下。
Let me clean this up.
我叫你们来是想让你们知道…
I called you all here to let you know that...
你今天剩下的时间可以休息。
that you have the rest of the day off.
你疯了吗?
Are you out of your mind?
如果我们休息几天，demo永远也准备不完。
We will never get the demo ready by taking days off.
我们甚至还没有开发Pixelcon展台。
We haven't even worked on our Pixelcon booth yet.
我听说Xodus要给他们七位数的收入。
I heard Xodus is dropping seven figures on theirs.
——七?-是的。
- Seven? - Yeah.
凯特?
Kate?
也许下午休息一下也无妨。
Maybe it couldn't hurt to take the afternoon off.
你知道的，好好享受一下。
You know, enjoy yourselves a little bit.
你一直工作很努力。
You've been working so hard.
去找点乐子。
Go have some fun.
-你应得的。-你是认真的?
- You deserve it. - Are you serious?
-我在…——听起来糟透了。
- What am I... - Sounds terrible.
我家里有两个十几岁的孩子。
I have two teenagers at home.
我从来没有休息过。
I've never had a day off.
我们在做什么?
What are we doing?
这是不好的。
This is bad.
你疯了吗?
Have you lost your mind?
我需要一些时间独自思考和工作
I need some time to think and work on my own
来解决这个问题。
to figure this out.
我爱你。开始工作。
I love you. Get to work.
嘿，你的员工要去哪里?
Hey, where are your employees going?
我说了他们想听的话。
I told them what they wanted to hear.
他们今天剩下的时间可以休息。
That they have the rest of the day off.
哈!最好的老板!
Huh! Best boss ever!
老兄,你猜怎么着?
Dude, guess what?
我给自己找了一份独立的研究
I got myself an independent study
所以现在我也可以一直待在这里了。
so now I can be here all the time too.
信贷。
For credit.
迪尔先生可能也能帮上忙。
You know, Mr. Diehl might be helpful too.
他设计了第一人称游戏
He designed that first-person game
我们小时候常玩的雅典娜9号
we used to play when we were kids, Athena 9.
不。那很酷,
No. That's cool,
但我认为编码与COBOL相比发生了一些变化。
but I think coding's changed a bit since COBOL.
好吧。那这就是你的无薪实习生了
Okay. Uh, then this is your unpaid intern
报告的责任。
reporting for duty.
我应该从哪里开始呢?
Where should I start?
我可以采访你，然后一起切
I can interview you and start cutting together
让我们来看看你迅速崛起的幕后故事……
a behind-the-scenes look at your meteoric rise...
好主意。千万别这么做。
Good idea. Just really don't do that.
好吧。
Okay.
你能给我一点独处的时间吗?
Can you just give me a little alone time?
我真的得开始了。
I really need to get started on this.
好吧。对了,明白了。
Okay. Right, gotcha.
酷。
Cool.
孤独。
Solitude.
完全得到它。
Totally get it.
如果你需要我，我在实习部。
I'll be in the intern department if you need me.
好吧?
All right?
不能发电子邮件?
Couldn't send an email?
♬直线♬
♪ Straight lines ♪
>展开你的翅膀，带我走吧
♪ Spread your wings And carry me now ♪
你让我感觉很好
♪ You make me feel good You make me ♪
♬你想感觉良好
♪ You wanna feel good ♪
嘿，发生什么事了?
Hey, what's going on?
我…我给员工放了几天假
I... I gave the staff a few days off
这样我就能独立工作了
so I could work on my own.
你不需要他们的帮助?
You don't need their help?
听起来既奇怪又孤独。
Sounds weird and lonely.
介意我加入吗?
Mind if I join?
——嗯…我不太……——谢谢!
- Uh... I'm not quite... - Thanks!
男人!
Man!
我在学校上过几门编程课
I've taken a couple of coding classes at school
但是…这是一个疯狂的小镇。
but... this is crazy town.
这些都是你自己做的?
You did all this yourself?
如何?
How?
我也解释不清楚。
I can't really explain it.
我听说我爸爸也是这样。
I heard my dad was the same way.
我不知道你爸怎么样，但是…
I don't know about your dad, but...
你妈妈给你打这针真是太棒了。
your mom is awesome for giving you this shot.
她这么信任你真是不可思议。
It's amazing how much she trusts you.
我有点希望我能像你妈妈一样。
I kind of wish I could be like your mom, you know.
只要能站在一群人面前
Just being able to get up in front of a group of people
并吸引所有人的注意。
and command everyone's attention.
你为什么不可以呢?
Why can't you?
我不知道。
I don't know.
我想我是唱诗班的摇滚歌手，
I think I rock it in a choir,
但当他们让我独唱时，
but when they ask me to sing solo though,
我只是有点……冻结。
I kinda just... freeze up.
这和我的想法正好相反。
That's like the opposite of me.
我只有一个人的时候才会编程。
I can only code when I'm on my own.
你得告诉我你是怎么做到的。
Okay, you gotta tell me how you did this.
比如你的大脑是怎么运作的。
Like how the hell your mind works.
都是0和1吗?
Is it all just zeros and ones?
有点。
Kinda.
编码的诀窍是理解
The trick to coding is understanding
每件事都要有正确的顺序
that everything has to be in the right order
否则就行不通了。
or it's not going to work.
但我看到的不只是0和1。
But I don't just see zeros and ones.
来，我来教你。
Here, let me show you.
当我在编程时，我看到了一个完全不同的世界。
When I'm coding, I see a whole other world.
一个一切皆有可能的世界。
A world where anything is possible.
梦想着你永远不会分享的梦想
♪ Dreaming the dreams You'll never share ♪
♬保持他们在黑暗中寻找火花
♪ Keep 'em in the dark Searching for a spark ♪
我们两个旋转，旋转，旋转
♪ Two of us spinning round Round and round ♪
你是怎么做到的?
How are you doing this?
♬这是开始♬
♪ This is the beginning ♪
Feel my feet Leaving the ground
♪ Feel my feet Leaving the ground ♪
♬在想什么可能仍然是♬
♪ Thinking about What might still be ♪
If i play my cards All right
♪ If I play my cards All right ♪
♬它让我彻夜难眠
♪ It keeps me up at night ♪
我们两个旋转
♪ Two of us spinning round ♪
♬旋转，旋转♬
♪ Spinning round and round ♪
♬这是开始♬
♪ This is the beginning ♪
Feel my feet Leaving the ground
♪ Feel my feet Leaving the ground ♪
♪哇哦哦哦哦哦♪
♪ Whoa oh oh oh oh ohh ♪
我梦见你在我的梦里
♪ I dream a dream of you ♪
♪哇哦哦哦哦哦♪
♪ Whoa oh oh oh oh ohh ♪
我梦想一个真实的梦
♪ I dream a dream that's true ♪
我梦见你在我的梦里
♪ I dream a dream of you ♪
特洛伊!检查它。
Troy! Check it.
魔法网的人送来了一个盒子。
A box from dudes who magic dot com just came.
你知道这是什么吧?
You know what this is, right?
哦，是的，我有。
Oh, yes I do.
帅哥谁魔法?
Dudes who magic?
我们已经做好了准备。
We're ready.
好了，大家都过来。
Alright, everybody, gather around.
他已经准备好了。
The man is ready.
什么?这是怎么呢发生什么事情了?
What? What's going on? What's happening?
三，二，一。
Three, two, and one.
空气中充满了电。
The air is charged with electricity.
每个人都焦急地等待
Everyone anxiously awaiting
特洛伊献礼的揭幕仪式
the unveiling of Troy's presentation.
你可以用电锯切断张力。
You can cut the tension with a chainsaw.
游戏玩家们，欢迎你们。
Playfield gamers, I bid you welcome.
这孩子知道怎么出场。
The boy knows how to make an entrance.
准备好进入一个奇幻王国吧，
Prepare to journey into a fantasy realm,
你凡人的眼睛从未见过的。
the likes of which your mortal eyes have never seen.
我将是你的向导
I will be your guide
我们将前往约特世界!
as we journey to the World of Yort!
Yort吗?
Yort?
一个圆顶帐篷，像一个圆形的帐篷。
A yurt, like a circular tent.
不,Yort。
No, Yort.
哦,好的。对不起。
Oh, okay. Sorry.
Yort !
Yort!
一种魔力野兽，可以把它的俘虏
A magical beast that bestows upon its captor
回到自己维度的能力。
the ability to return to their own dimension.
输入……如果你敢。
Enter... if you dare.
嗯,我敢。
Well, I dare.
我们的游戏从这里开始，
Our game begins here,
在三蟾蜍酒馆。
in the Tavern of the Three Toads.
你们每个人将选择你的角色
Each of you will choose your character
from one of five different archetype, yes.from one of five different archetype, yes.from one of five different archetype, yes
from one of five different archetypes, yes.
骑士……小偷…
The knight... the thief...
野蛮人…
barbarian...
和尚……或向导。
monk... or the wizard.
这就像一个标准的RPG。
So, it's like a standard RPG.
嘘，让他来配音。
Shhh, let him do the voices.
从那里，你将独自前往另一个过去
From there, you will journey alone to an alternate past
你的冒险将从哪里开始。
where your adventure will begin.
然而，危险无处不在。
Danger lurks at every turn, however.
小心影子人!
Beware the Shadow People!
在荒地…
Survive the wasteland...
冒险到熔岩王的城堡去!
and venture to the keep of the Lava King!
Rooooar !
Rooooar!
对不起,我很抱歉。
Sorry, I'm sorry.
我…我需要坐下来。
I... I need to sit down.
这是好的,林登,
It's alright, Lyndon,
我想我们已经听够了。
I think we've heard just about enough.
这两天你就干了这些吗?
So, is this all you've been working on the last two days?
是的，大人。
It is, my lord.
就这些吗?
That's it?
你根本没在研究杰克豪斯吗?
You haven't been working on Jackhouse at all?
嗯…不。
Um... no.
好吧，可爱的小游戏。
Okay, well, cute little play.
凯特，我不知道你想让我们做什么。
Kate, I mean, I'm not sure what you expect us to do.
他只花了我们两天时间。
He just cost us two days.
没什么好炫耀的。
There's nothing to show for it.
听着，我们让甘道夫带领我们越久，
Look, the longer we let Gandalf lead us,
我们失去一切的机会就越大。
the greater our chance is we're gonna lose everything.
我们现在得把注意力集中到杰克豪斯身上!
We need to start focusing on Jackhouse now!
吉米,Jackhouse糟透了。
Jimmy, Jackhouse sucks.
-不，他没有!——好吧,好吧。
- Oh no, he didn't! - Okay, okay.
这就够了。这两个你。好吧?
That's enough. Both of you. All right?
让我给你看看我们面对的是什么。
Let me show you what we're up against.
>欢迎来到地狱星球
Welcome to Planet Hell.
You will never be prepared.你永远不会有准备
You will never be prepared.
哇，好多啊。
Whoa, that's a lot.
1亿外星人
One hundred million aliens.
外星人太多了!
There's too many aliens!
好了，现在让我痛苦地说清楚。
Okay, now to make it painfully clear.
粉碎,粉碎,粉碎。
Smashing, smashing, smashing.
Smash, smash, smash.
特洛伊，说实话，在他们的帮助下，
Troy, can you honestly, with their help,
所有这些都及时准备好了吗?
get all of this ready in time?
绝对的。
Absolutely.
我们需要的东西都贴在墙上了。
Everything we need is up on these walls.
每个人的说明书上都标有自己的名字。
Everyone's instructions are labeled with their name.
那好吧，全速前进直到Pixelcon，好吗?
All right then, full speed 'til Pixelcon, okay?
什么都没有。
Nothing else.
对不起,吉米。
Sorry, Jimmy.
Chay-roof吗?
Chay-roof?
我敢肯定这里面肯定有个游戏
Well, I'm sure that there's a game somewhere
在这个工艺品项目中，
in this arts and crafts project,
但至少还有六个月。
but it's at least six months away.
好吧。我们还有什么选择，吉米?
Okay. What choice do we have, Jimmy?
在Jackhouse工作。
Work on Jackhouse.
你也看到我们面对的是什么了。
You saw what we were up against.
我就像在对着一堵墙说话。
It's like I'm talking to a wall.
特洛伊，没用的。这些都不管用。
Troy, it's not working. None of this is working.
伙计们，画得很清楚。
Guys, the drawings are crystal clear.
是什么问题?
What's the problem?
没有足够的内存来缓存所有这些资产。
There's not enough memory to cache all these assets.
此外，我们还需要修复对库的API调用。
Also, we need to fix the API call to the library.
太空巫师是如何叙事的
How does the space wizard narrative
与城堡故事相吻合?
dovetail into the castle story?
伙计们,伙计们!
Guys, guys!
能占用你一分钟吗?
Can I have a minute?
独自一人吗?
Alone, please?
好吧，但有很多东西
Okay, but there's a lot of stuff
-这说不通啊。——请。
- that doesn't make any sense. - Please.
它的形状有两个选择。
There's two options of the shape of it.
我没见过那把斧头。我很高兴那不是我的。
I haven't seen that axe. I'm glad it's not mine.
我一整天都在看这个，
I've been looking at this all day,
这说不通啊。
and it doesn't make any sense.
妈妈……
Mom...
这些人，他们不…他们他们已经…
these people, they don't... they they're already just...
我就不能自己做吗?
can't I just do this on my own?
他们只会让我慢下来。
They're just going to slow me down.
亲爱的，我也说过同样的话
Honey, I had this exact same conversation
你父亲就在这个房间里
with your father right in this very room
12年前,
12 years ago,
他最终意识到了这点
and he eventually realized that
他们都有自己的贡献。
they all have something to contribute.
你能想个办法和他们合作吗?
Could you please figure out a way to work with them?
我可以试一试。
I can try.
你应该做得比尝试更好。
You gotta do better than try.
这些人也是我的家人。
These people are also family to me.
我知道,妈妈。
I know, Mom.
我知道。
I know.
和吉米。
And Jimmy too.
你把他的工作搞得一团糟。
You kinda took a crap all over his work.
他心烦意乱。
He's upset.
我以为那家伙是刀枪不入的。
I thought that guy was bulletproof.
如果你在做某件事，你会有什么感觉
How would you feel if you worked on something
一年多来，
for over a year,
有个年轻的高手进来了，年纪只有你一半，
and some young hotshot came in, half your age,
然后完全撕碎?
and completely shredded it?
那孩子应该八岁
Well, that kid would be eight,
那将是不可思议的。
and that would be incredible.
好吧，但吉米是个很有天赋的游戏设计师。
Okay, but Jimmy is a really talented game designer.
他是。只是我们走错了路
He is. It's just we went down the wrong path
和他在一起太久了。
with him for too long.
总之，总有一天，你会需要吉米的帮助。
Anyway, at some point, you are gonna need Jimmy's help.
好吧,我试试看。
Okay, I'll try.
我是说，我会的。
I mean, I will.
好吧。
Okay.
啊,妈妈?
Ah, Mom?
是的。
Yeah.
再次感谢。
Thanks again.
没什么。
It's nothing.
特洛伊，过来。
Troy, get over here.
那么，药物有帮助吗?
So, are the meds helping?
因为你看起来很糟。
'Cause you look terrible.
这是你的专业医学意见吗?
Is that your professional medical opinion?
凯特…
Kate...
在最糟糕的时候，多发性硬化症会露出丑陋的头。
MS rears its ugly head at the worst times.
你只需要多休息。
You just need to get more rest.
医生的命令。
Doctor's orders.
我是你的医生。
And I'm your doctor.
我们不能再这样见面了。
We have to stop meeting like this.
距离Pixelcon还有20天。
Pixelcon is 20 days away.
网络上在热议什么?
What's the Internet buzzing about?
球场的新游戏,
Playfield's new game,
我讨厌听到的关于这东西的每一件事。
I hate every single thing I'm hearing about this thing.
不好的。肯定不是很好。
Not good. Definitely not good.
我已经……我从来没有对电子游戏如此兴奋过
I've... literally never been more excited for a video game
比我对Xodus的外星收割者更有信心。
than I am for Xodus' Alien Reaper.
我现在就要。
I need it now.
《外星死神》就是这样的游戏
Alien Reaper is the kind of game
你最好的噩梦都是由它组成的。
that your best nightmares are made of.
我听说Xodus花了一千万美元
I heard Xodus spent 10 million dollars
只在过场动画上。
on the cut scenes alone.
当你在一个游戏上投入那么多钱时，
When you're dropping that kind of cash on a game,
对于独立开发者来说，竞争是不可能的。
it is impossible for the indies to compete.
老实说，操场看起来一团糟。
Honestly, Playfield is looking like a mess.
没有好,朋友。
No bueno, friends.
求你了，操场，求你乖乖的。
Please, Playfield, please be good.
要比最近更好。
Be better than you've been recently.
- You were so great…——嘿。
- You were so great... - Hey.
-…回到以前。 -你在看什么?
- ... back in the day. - What'cha looking at?
球迷们的期望让我很紧张。
Just getting nervous over all the fans' expectations.
我明白了。
Yeah, I get it.
你不想让任何人失望。
You don't want to let anyone down.
是的,有人吗?
Yeah, does anyone?
呃，我有点习惯了。
Eh, I'm kinda used to it.
相信我。
Believe me.
特洛伊，我不明白你那愚蠢的海报!
Troy, I don't understand your dumb poster!
我恨你逼我这么做!
I hate you for making me do this!
我给你看样东西。
Hey, let me show you something.
我能看看你的手机吗?
Can I see your phone?
是的。
Yeah.
酷,嗯…
Cool, um...
在那里。
There.
检查出来。
Check it out.
它是什么?
What is it?
这是一个定制的增强现实程序
It's a custom augmented reality program
怯场。
for stage fright.
是啊，他们说最好的办法是
Yeah, they say the best thing to do
就是在人群中专注于一个人。
is focus on one person in a crowd.
找一张友善的脸
Find a friendly face
就好像你只跟他们说话一样。
and it's like you're only talking to them.
我都不知道他们有这个。
I didn't even know they had those.
不,他们没有。
No, they don't.
但我……这是我做的。
But I... I built this one.
给你。
For you.
你哪来的时间?
Where did you find the time?
我挤出了时间。
I made the time.
嗯,我要……
Uh, I gotta...
-是的。-是的。
- Yeah. - Yeah.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
是的，是的，进来吧。
Yeah, yeah, come on in.
是的，特洛伊，整个部分
So yeah, Troy, that whole section
在站立会议上没有提到。
was not covered in the stand-up meeting.
这还不包括我们一直在做的事情。
That doesn't factor in what we've been working on.
我还有一个问题关于……
I have another question about...
拜托!
Please!
螺丝。
Screw it.
我知道,这是……这是一个不同的…
I know, it's... it's a different...
这将是一件不同的事情。
it's gonna be a different thing.
特洛伊，我们得谈谈。
Troy, we need to talk.
我现在没时间，吉米。
I don't have any time right now, Jimmy.
有一条线。而我在这上面。
There's a line. And I'm at the top of it.
我说了我们得谈谈。
I said we need to talk.
爸爸?
Daddy?
艾米丽，你在这干嘛?
Emily, what are you doing here?
我和爷爷一起来的。
I came with Grandpa.
他在你办公室等着呢。
He's waiting in your office.
啊…好吧。
Ah... okay.
我马上回来。
I'm gonna be right back.
艾米你在那等着好吗
Em, you just wait there, okay?
粉碎,粉碎,粉碎。
Smashing, smashing, smashing.
粉碎,粉碎,粉碎。粉碎。
Smash, smash, smash. Smashing.
先生,你早。
Sir, you're early.
房地产有自己的运行时间表，吉米。
Real estate operates on its own timetable, Jimmy.
我还是不敢相信我唯一的儿子
I still can't believe my only son
以玩电子游戏为生。
plays video games for a living.
你什么时候才能长大，找份真正的工作?
When are you going to grow up and get a real job?
爸爸，这是份真正的工作。
Dad, this is a real job.
不如你下个月来Pixelcon吧
You know what, why don't you come to Pixelcon next month
我会让你看看我能做什么
and I'll show you what I can do.
——小精灵吗?——Pixelcon。
- Pixie cut? - Pixelcon.
这是一个大型电子游戏大会我要在那里首次推出这个游戏
It's a big video game convention where I'm gonna debut the game
我一整年都在做的事
I've been workin' on all year.
一年吗?在一场比赛吗?
One year? On one game?
这整个环境让我感到恶心。
This whole environment makes me sick to my stomach.
我只希望艾米丽不要…
I just hope that Emily doesn't...
哦，管它呢。
Oh, the hell with it.
不,继续。说出来。
No, go on. Say it.
你希望艾米丽不会什么?
You hope that Emily doesn't what?
我希望她不会思考
I hope that she doesn't think
这就是现实世界的运作方式。
this is how the real world works.
艾米，你拿的是什么?
Hey Em, what've you got there?
这是赛尔达的N64模拟器。
It's an N64 emulator of Zelda.
陶笛吗?
Ocarina?
宫本茂。
Shigeru Miyamoto.
没有他，开放世界根本就不存在。
Without him, open worlds wouldn't even exist.
我听说第一部很有灵感
Yeah, I heard the first one was inspired
因为他喜欢洞穴探险。
by his love of spelunking.
优秀的设计师是基于自己的游戏
Well, the great designers base their games
他们喜欢的东西，那个人喜欢洞穴探险。
on stuff they love, and that man loved spelunking.
听着，我们得转移注意力。
Look, we need to shift our focus.
我们需要创造一个可玩的Jackhouse演示版本。
We need to build a playable demo of Jackhouse.
——什么?-更近了
- What? - It's much closer
而不是《特洛伊世界》
than World of Troy.
Yort。
Yort.
是的,不管。
Yeah, whatever.
听着，如果我们不完成其中一个游戏，
Look, if we don't finish one of the games,
我们什么都卖不出去了。
we're not gonna have anything to sell.
我知道。
I know that.
所以我们必须干掉尤尔特。
Which is why we have to finish Yort.
你为什么不想参与我的游戏?
Why don't you want to work on my game?
吉米，先别管漏洞和可扩展性了
Jimmy, forget about the bugs and the scalability for a second
想想看。
and just think about it.
谁想玩一款唯一目标的游戏
Who wants to play a game where your only goal
是要毁坏房屋吗?
is to destroy houses?
我猜每个人都想成为神奇的树蛞蝓
Oh, and I guess everybody wants to be a magical tree slug
穿越时间去寻找神秘的野兽?
flying through time in search of a mystical beast?
嗯,有点。
Well, kinda.
这是我唯一的一份工作。
This is the only job I've ever had.
我帮助建立了这家公司。
I helped build this company.
我现在有了自己的家庭
I have my own family now,
你还逼我做我不想做的事!
and you are making me do something I don't wanna do!
吉米，你没有迷你游戏
Jimmy, you have no mini-games,
没有分段，就没有经济。
no subsections, no economy.
电钻是唯一的核心循环。
Jackhammering is your only core loop.
就好像你忘记了这些游戏是关于什么的。
It's like you forgot what these games are all about.
哦,来吧。
Em, come on.
怎么了,吉米?今天要花半天时间?
What's up, Jimmy? Takin' a half day today?
你可以保留你的moba
You can keep your MOBAs
和第一人称射击游戏
and your first person shooters
，你可以推你的battle royale
and you can shove your battle royale
where the sun don't shine. .where the sun don't shine. . .
where the sun don't shine.
>  >  >  >  >  >
Forget MMOs and open worlds.
在Playfield Games，这里有一种新的游戏
Here at Playfield Games, there's a new kind of game,
from a new kind mastermind.
from a new kind of mastermind.
. Playfield is about to change games forever. . Playfield将永远改变游戏
Playfield is about to change games forever.
竞争情况如何?
And what of the competition?
Xodus糟透了。
Xodus sucks.
Xodus sucks♬
♪ Xodus sucks ♪
♬X-xodus sucks♬
♪ X-xodus sucks ♪
♬Xodus Xodus Xodus Xodus♬
♪ Xodus Xodus Xodus Xodus ♪
♬Sucks Sucks Sucks Xodus Sucks♬
♪ Sucks sucks sucks Xodus sucks ♪
♬Xodus Xodus Xodus Xodus♬
♪ Xodus Xodus Xodus Xodus ♪
Xodus sucks♬
♪ Xodus sucks ♪
Xodus糟透了。
Xodus sucks.
哦，哦，上传然后爆炸。
Oh, oh, upload and boom.
你有时间吗?
Hey, you got a sec?
是的，是的，我喜欢。我确实有时间。
Yeah, yeah, I do. I do have a sec.
我有很多秒。
I have a ton of secs.
事实上，我有很多秒。
In fact, I have like all the secs.
嗯…(我不是那个意思。)
Um... that is not what I meant.
你把事情搞得很诡异。
You do a really good job at making things weird.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我只是来告诉你，我报名了我的第一个独唱。
I just came to tell you, I signed up for my first solo.
很神奇的。
Amazing.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
只是…每个人都远远落在后面
Just... everyone's falling so far behind
我只是…我没法让他们拿到。
and I just... I can't get them to get it.
是的,我听说过。
Yeah, I heard.
你的计划是什么?
So, what's your plan?
既然我没法让他们理解，
Well, since I can't get them to understand,
今晚我会自己修复核心渲染引擎
I'll fix the core rendering engine myself tonight
然后可能只是…
then probably just...
——嘿,嘿!-…多工作一点……
- Hey, hey! - ...work a bit more...
我才来了两周，
I've only been here like two weeks so,
也许我不知道，
maybe I don't know,
但我从没见过你向别人求助。
but I've never seen you ask for help from anyone.
特洛伊?
Troy?
特洛伊。
Troy.
也许从现在开始。
Maybe start now.
好吧，听着，这机会不大，
Okay, listen, this is a long shot,
但我一直在看吉米的杰克豪斯地图
but I've been going over Jimmy's Jackhouse maps
如果我们让他们改信尤尔
and if we convert them for Yort,
我们可以在一周内完成6个关卡。
we could get six levels in a week.
真的吗?那么快?
Really? That much that fast?
这意味着……
Which means...
我们这周就能完成我的游戏。
We would finish my game this week.
那太棒了。
That would be awesome.
好吧，我会让玛丽开始查的。
Okay, well, I'll get Marie started on that.
谢谢你,劳拉。
Thanks, Laura.
我真的以为你不喜欢我。
I really thought you didn't like me.
我不。
I do not.
我这么做是为了凯特。
I'm doing this for Kate.
密码?
Password?
玛丽，我需要你的帮助。
Hey, Marie, I need your help.
我的天，终于来了。
Oh my gosh, finally.
我知道只要我有耐心，
I knew that if I was just patient,
我最终会有机会的
I would eventually get my chance
对了，我有一些关于约特的好主意。
and, hey, I have some great ideas for Yort.
我相信你会的，
I'm sure you do,
但我现在真正需要你做的是
but what I really need you to do right now
是要重制杰克豪斯的故事线吗
is to rework the storylines from Jackhouse
与尤特同步。
to sync with Yort.
明白了。
Gotcha.
好，我把这些概念都归档
Okay, so I'll just file away all these concepts
我一直在头脑风暴。
that I've been brainstorming.
谢谢你,玛丽!
Thanks, Marie!
什么……
What the...
什么……?
What the...?
抱歉，林登。
Hey, sorry about that, Lyndon.
-这是怎么回事?——我们的财务。
- What is all this? - Our financials.
我得把它们传真给Xodus。
I gotta fax them over to Xodus.
我们没有传真机。
We don't have a fax machine.
我一直在用什么?
Well, what've I been using?
你为什么要把我们的财务报表发给Xodus?
Why are you sending our financials to Xodus?
儿子，你妈还能怎么保住你的房子?
Son, how else is your mom gonna keep your house?
是的。
Yeah.
妈，你把我们的房子抵押了?
Mom, you had to mortgage our house?
对不起,蜂蜜。
I'm sorry, honey.
We're out of money.我们没钱了
We're out of money.
> i had to buy us time to get to Pixelcon. .
I had to buy us time to get to Pixelcon.
只要你不接受Xodus的交易。
As long as you don't take that Xodus deal.
尤尔特就要准备好了。
Yort is going to be ready.
劳拉和玛丽终于开始明白了
Laura and Marie are finally starting to get it
就连吉米和我也有点亲密了
and even Jimmy and I are kind of bonding.
所以…别担心,妈妈。
So... don't worry, Mom.
You're dealing with so much.(你应付的太多了。
You're dealing with so much.
对不起，我的医生不让我去办公室
I'm sorry, but my doctor won't let me go to the office
. . . . . . . .
until this flare-up subsides.
我希望我能和你在一起，但是我相信你
I wish I could be there with you, but I trust you.
谢谢。
Thanks.
好吧,再见。爱你。
Okay, bye. Love you.
哦,不。
Oh, no.
Xodus一塌糊涂。
Xodus Sucks.
X-Xodus一塌糊涂。
X-Xodus Sucks.
有一种新的游戏
There's a new kind of game
from a new kind mastermind.
from a new kind of mastermind.
. Playfield is about to change games forever. . Playfield将永远改变游戏
Playfield is about to change games forever.
… ?
...where the sun don't shine.
Xo-Xo-Xo-Xodus一塌糊涂。
Xo-Xo-Xo-Xodus Sucks.
Playfield is about to change. . .
Playfield is about to change.
Xodus一塌糊涂。
Xodus sucks.
哦,糟了!
Oh, crap!
尼克!
Nick!
尼克，你做了什么?
Nick, what did you do?
太棒了,对吧?
Awesome, right?
已经有成千上万的浏览量了!
Thousands of views already!
我明确告诉过你不要这么做!
I specifically told you not to do this!
你真的在生我的气吗?
Are you like actually mad at me?
是的!
Yes!
你让我的生活变得比以前难了十倍。
You just made my life like 10 times harder.
那我该怎么补救呢?
Well, how can I fix it?
我该怎么办?
What can I do?
没有什么!
Nothing!
因为你什么也做不了。
Because there's nothing you can do.
我要回学校了。
I'm going back to school.
尼克……
Nick...
尼克。我是说现在。
Nick. I meant right now.
我只是想帮忙。
I was just trying to help.
尼克,快点。
Nick, come on.
吉米?什么?
Jimmy? What?
好吧，我来做你的性格测试。
Okay, I'll do your personality quiz.
“你是哪个《老友记》角色?”
"Which Friends character are you?"
是的,好的。
Yes, okay.
Chandler到底是谁?
Who the hell is Chandler?
很好，当然，死亡之球。
Ah, great, of course, beachball of death.
不。不，不，不，不，不!
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
玛丽,有什么事吗?
Marie, what's up?
我的电脑在工作的中途死机了，
My computer just froze up in the middle of everything,
而且它不让我重启。
and it's not letting me reboot.
呃,我……我也一样。
Uh, me... me too, the same thing.
特洛伊，你做了什么?
Troy, what did you do?
你什么意思?我的电脑冻结了,
What do you mean? My computer froze,
所以我正要去厨房吃点东西。
so I was just going to the kitchen to get a snack.
它不是冷冻的，它是条虫子。
It's not frozen, it's a worm.
什么?不，那不可能。
What? No, that's not possible.
你把你的电脑设置成集线器
You set up your computer to be the hub
专门的网络，记得吗?
of the dedicated network, remember?
哦,不。
Oh, no.
它粘在这个网页上了。
It's stuck on this webpage.
劳拉是正确的!你下载了一个蠕虫!
Laura's right! You downloaded a worm!
它会吞噬我们的网络
It's gonna eat through our network
摧毁我们所有的硬件。
and destroy all of our hardware.
-我们得切断电源!——对,好吧!
- We need to cut the power! - Right, okay!
不是你的力量!
Not your power!
我们得切断整栋楼的电源!
We need to cut the power to the whole building!
蠕虫?
A worm?
做了……我们及时阻止了吗?
Did... did we stop it in time?
怎么会这样呢?
How could this happen?
特洛伊，你离开办公室之前在做什么?
Troy, what were you doing before you left your office?
什么都没有。我…
Nothing. I'd...
我打开了吉米的一封邮件，里面有一个链接。
I'd opened an email from Jimmy that had a link in it.
他不会。
He wouldn't.
——没有。-他看起来很生气
- No way. - He seemed pretty pissed
就在他离开之前。
right before he left.
他留下了这张纸条。
He left this note.
林登，再打开断路器。
Lyndon, go flip the breaker again.
特洛伊，什么都别碰。
Troy, don't touch anything.
让我们看看造成了多大的伤害。
Let's see how much damage was done.
断路器。
Breaker.
这些计算机完全瘫痪了。
The computers are completely fried.
甚至备份服务器。
Even the backup servers.
一切都消失了。
Everything's gone.
但是,呃…这是不是意味着……
But, uh... does this mean...
我们从两场比赛到零场比赛。
We went from two games to none.
我们……我们得告诉凯特。
We... we gotta tell Kate.
我会告诉她的。
I'll tell her.
嗯。
Huh.
特洛伊，亲爱的，是你吗?
Troy, honey, is that you?
是的，妈妈，是我。
Yeah, Mom, it's me.
很抱歉这么长时间没上网了。
I'm sorry I've been offline for such a long time now.
我还没有……我好久没发作得这么厉害了。
I haven't... I haven't had a flare-up this bad in forever.
Yort会怎么样?
How's Yort going?
很好。
It's good.
我只是希望我能多帮点忙。
I just wish I could help more.
你有什么想说的吗?
Is there anything you want to talk about?
嗯…不是真的。
Um... not really.
我只是想确认你感觉好些了
I just wanted to make sure you're feeling better
这样你就可以在主要活动上展示了。
so you can present at the main event.
你确定在那之前我不在你能行吗?
Are you sure you'll be okay without me until then?
好的，我知道了。
Yeah, I got it.
我只是…只是来拿套换洗衣服
I was just... just coming to get a change of clothes
我就回办公室了
and I'll head back to the office.
爱您,妈妈。
Love you, Mom.
爱你。
Love you.
心碎碰撞
♪ Broken hearts collide ♪
♪ Now we're telling All these lies ♪
♬只是为了让它感觉好起来，我只是需要让你走
♪ Just to make it feel alright I just need to let you go ♪
嘿。
Hey.
有交会吗?
Got a sec?
看起来你正在做
It looks like you're doing
外面正在打扫房子呢。
some serious housecleaning out there.
每个人的辞职。
Everyone's quitting.
这是……那不是很好。
That's... that's not good.
也许这能让你感觉好点。
Hey, maybe this will make you feel better.
是一个u盘，还有一盘混音带。
It's a thumb drive, and a mix tape.
我创作并表演了它。
I wrote and performed it.
这是你游戏的主题曲。
It's the theme song for your game.
再也没有约特了，佩吉。
There's no more Yort, Paige.
Playfield Games也不再存在了。
There's no more Playfield Games either.
什么?
What?
嘿,大家好!快来看这个!
Hey, everyone! Come check this out!
看看我找到的这张旧DVD。
Look at this old DVD I found.
这是经典的吉米-磨砂的小费。
That is classic Jimmy - frosted tips.
至少有10年的历史了。
That must be at least 10 years old.
12左右。
Around 12.
就在我们发行了第一款游戏后。
It's right after we released our first game.
这是Playfield Games的历史。
This is Playfield Games history.
嘿,嘿,Mayfielders !
Hey, hey, Mayfielders!
我们有世界上最好的工作!我说的对吗?
We have the best jobs in the world! Am I right?
伙计，那家伙太棒了。
Man, that guy was great.
看，我知道你们一直在努力工作
Look, I know how hard you've all been working
在过去几个月
over the last several months...
但是，如果我们已经从过去的一年里学到了什么，那么，
But, if we've learned anything from the past year,
跌宕起伏，
the ups and downs,
乔治和我都觉得是什么让它真正特别
George and I both feel that what makes it truly special
是和你关心的人一起做
is doing it with the people you care about.
- i>是的，亲爱的。 -是的。
- That's right, honey. - Yeah.
哦!
Oh!
你知道，直到我关闭这个，打开这些
You know, it wasn't until I shut this and opened these
， this game became something special.， this game became something special.， this game became something special.
that this game became something special.
It's so much more than a game.这不仅仅是一场游戏
It's so much more than just a game.
这是关于你们每一个人的
It's about each and every one of you.
It's about all of us.这是关于我们所有人的
It's about all of us.
这就是为什么我们决定改变
And that's why we've decided to change
我们公司的名字从Mayfield Games到
the name of our company from Mayfield Games to...
击鼓声,林登!
drumroll, Lyndon!
球场游戏!
Playfield Games!
啊!
Woo-hoo!
是的,t恤,吉米。
Yes, T-shirts, Jimmy.
我希望，呃，我们希望，这是一个place
And I hope, uh, we hope, that this is a place
you can always feel at home.你总是感觉像在家里一样
you can always feel at home.
If you're at Playfield, you're always be.如果你在Playfield，你就永远在这里
If you're at Playfield, you always will be.
We're never gonna let you down.我们永远不会让你失望
We're never gonna let you down.
不打算让你走，
Not going to let you go,
i>因为你们是我们的家人
because, you guys, you're our family.
你们每一个人。
Each and every one of you.
林登，玛丽，吉米，劳拉
Lyndon, Marie, Jimmy, Laura.
我的意思是，如果没有你，我们就不会在这里
I mean, we wouldn't be here without you.
And we wouldn ' t want to be.
And we would never want to be.
我们希望有一天我们的儿子会去工作
And we hope that someday our son will get to work
i>with people as incredible as you guys.我和像你们一样不可思议的人在一起
with people as incredible as you guys.
特洛伊，你觉得我们的新名字怎么样?
What do you think, Troy, of our new name?
球场游戏规则!
Playfield Games rules!
特洛伊，你觉得怎么样?
What do you think, Troy?
你想哪天和爸爸一起工作吗?
Do you want to come work with Daddy someday?
——是的。 - ，好的
- Yeah. - Yeah, alright.
这是什么……?
What's this...?
嗨,尼克。
Hey, Nick.
嘿。你在这里干什么?
Hey. What are you doin' here?
我来找你。
I came looking for you.
你的…你妈妈说你会在这里。
Your... your mom said you'd be here.
好吧,嗯…
Okay, well...
我只是顺路过来看看有没有什么东西。
I just stopped by to see if I had somethin' here.
所以，我来学校不是为了玩…无论什么。
So, it's not like I'm here at school for fun... whatever.
不，不，当然不是。
No, no, of course not.
所以,找到了。
So, found it.
这里的。
It's here.
所以嗯…是的…
So um... yeah...
我要走了…
I'm just gonna go...
和其他新朋友一起玩。
and hang out with my other new friends.
你知道那个视频给我带来了一万名新订户吗?
You know that video got me 10,000 new subscribers?
他们称自己为昵称。
They call themselves the Nicknames.
朗朗上口的。
Catchy.
是的。
Yeah.
嗨,尼克。我…我明白了。
Hey, Nick. I... I get it.
你拍那个视频只是为了帮我。
You were only making that video 'cause you wanted to help me.
我在操场的时候脑子不太清楚，好吗?
I was in way over my head at Playfield, all right?
我不该说那些话的
I shouldn't have said any of the things
我对你说的…或任何人。
that I said to you... or to anyone.
我做了这个视频。
I made the video.
你叫我别这么做的。但我还是做了。
You told me not to. I did it anyway.
这是我的不好。我很抱歉。
That's my bad. I'm sorry.
尼克，我不知道还能找谁。
Nick, I just, I didn't know who else to turn to.
Yort是完蛋了。
Yort is screwed.
我下载了这个蠕虫
I downloaded this worm,
和…我们的电脑都坏了。
and... and our computers just got fried.
我告诉过你不要去那些网站。
I told you not to visit those sites.
尼克，我们的游戏输掉了密码。
Nick, we lost the code to our games.
整个代码?
The entire code?
是的。
Yeah.
我只是…我需要有人帮我弄清楚下一步该做什么。
I just... I need some help figuring out what to do next.
你说你需要帮助?
You said you need help?
-是的。是的。-你说你需要帮助。
- Yeah. Yes. - You said you need help.
我得到了你的帮助!来吧!
I got your help! Come on!
哦!
Oh!
嗨,迪先生。迪先生吗?
Hey, Mr. Diehl. Mr. Diehl?
啊,尼克!
Ahhh, Nick!
梅菲尔德吗?
Mayfield?
我以为你被停职了?
I thought you were suspended?
春假。
It's spring break.
一遍吗?
Again?
迪尔先生偷偷溜过来跟你玩电子游戏。
Look, Mr. Diehl sneaks away here to play your video games.
伙计，那些游戏应该是给我们玩的。
Dude, those games were supposed to be just for us.
他就像特洛伊游戏迷。
He's like a Troy game junkie.
啊!我是特洛伊游戏迷!
Ahh! I'm a total Troy game junkie!
我是你爸爸的超级粉丝。
And I was a big fan of your dad's.
嘿,你看。还记得吗?他是雅典娜9号的主角。
Hey, look. Remember? He was the lead guy on Athena 9.
我是主角。他说我是主角。
I was the lead guy. He said I was the lead guy.
然后Xodus把我解雇了。
And then Xodus laid me off.
把它写下来，这就是我学到的
Get it in writing, that's what I learned
从那里的经历。
from that experience right there.
没有消息，没有遣散费，什么都没有。
No word, no severance package, nothing.
然后我不得不回家找我妻子……噢,
Then I had to go home to my wife... oooh,
这个…这个女人是另一回事…
this... this woman is something else...
天啊，你能告诉他精彩的部分吗!
Oh my god, could you just tell him the good part!
的游戏。
The games.
…哦,对,对。
The... oh, right, right.
他在你们公司做营销副总裁的时候…
Well, while he was VP of marketing at your company...
你是这么告诉他的吗?
Is that what you told him?
．..我求他给我一份你新游戏的代码。
...I begged him to give me a copy of the code of your new games.
Wh……等待,…哪一个?
Wh... wait, which... which ones?
你知道的，尤特和杰克豪斯。
You know, the Yort and Jackhouse.
我只是想看看他们。
I just wanted to see 'em.
我没跟任何人说。我向你保证。
I didn't share 'em with anyone. I promise you.
等等，你有密码的副本吗?
Wait, so, you have a copy of the code?
对，对，就在那儿。
Yeah, yeah, it's right there.
尼克，你给了他一份密码?
Nick, you gave him a copy of the code?
这就是我想告诉你的!
That's what I was trying to tell you!
——这是它!——好的。
- That's it!. - Okay.
好了，小声点。
Alright, tone it down.
——电脑!——啊!
- The computers! - Ahhh!
嘿。
Hey.
你不是在说我们赢的电脑，好吗?
You're not talking about those computers we won - okay?
天啊，这些孩子。
Oh my god, these kids.
你们能把这些启动吗?
Can you guys get these up and running?
-好吧。-我有工作要做。
- Uh-huh, all right. - I've got some work to do.
并调用每一个人。
And call everyone.
好吧。
All right.
他们得到它!
They got it!
Yort Jackhouse !他们把两个都干掉了。
Yort and Jackhouse! They got them both.
你手动备份了文件?
You manually backed up the files?
不，不是我。是尼克和迪尔先生
No, no, it wasn't me. It was Nick and Mr. Diehl,
但你们觉得我们有可能
but do you guys think it's possible for us
才能及时恢复正常吗?
to get back up and running in time?
有合适的硬件，但只有一个人
With the right hardware, but there's only one guy
谁知道怎么操纵那些地图。
who knows how to manipulate those maps.
那家伙现在在卖公寓。
And that guy is currently selling condos.
一小时后在高中见我!
Meet me at the high school in an hour!
啊。
Ah.
我最好给优步打个电话。
I-I better call Uber.
那些猪在毯子里吗?
Are those pigs in a blanket?
仅供潜在买家使用。
For prospective buyers only.
你怎么找到我的?
How did you find me?
你爸爸的传单到处都是。
Your dad's flyers are everywhere.
好吧，你为什么要找我?
Okay, why did you find me?
吉米，我从没听过你的话
Jimmy, I never listened to you
这是……这是一个错误。
and that was... that was a mistake.
我现在才意识到我对你有多糟糕，
And I realize now just how terrible I was to you,
我真的很抱歉
and I'm really sorry.
你不好意思吗?
You're sorry?
哇。
Wow.
好了，现在轮到你了。
Well, now it's your turn.
我为什么要道歉?
What am I sorry for?
因为你发了那封愚蠢的人格测试邮件
For sending that email with that dumb personality quiz
差点毁了整个公司?
that almost destroyed the entire company?
个性……?什么电子邮件?
Personality...? What email?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你发的邮件感染了我们所有的电脑。
You sent an email that infected all of our computers.
不,我没有。我不会那么做的。
No, I didn't. I would never do that.
如果不是你，那是谁干的?
Well, if it wasn't you, then who did it?
我不管DNA怎么说，
I don't care what the DNA says,
我在否认亲子关系，好吗?呀。
I'm denying paternity, all right? Jeez.
嘿，瑞克，我不想打断你，但是……它工作。
Hey Rick, I hate to interrupt, but... it worked.
他们被木马病毒咬了?
They bit on the Trojan worm?
是的。哈!
Yeah. Ha!
“你是哪个《老友记》角色?”
"Which Friends character are you?"
整个公司都是一群乔伊。
That whole company is a bunch of Joeys.
市场营销已经开始准备复古游戏了吗
Have marketing start prepping a retro release
所有Playfield的老游戏。
for all of Playfield's old games.
现在凯特得接受我的条件了。
Now Kate's gonna have to take my deal.
Andale !这意味着现在!
Ándale! That means now!
是的,先生。
Si, señor.
就算你没发那封邮件，
Even if you didn't send that email,
你还是抛弃了我们。
you still abandoned us.
我放弃了你?
I abandoned you?
你有想过吗
Did you even think for one second
如果游乐场关门，艾米丽会怎么样?
what could happen to Emily if Playfield closed?
因为我每天都这么做。
Because I did, every single day.
你对我太糟糕了。你在扼杀公司!
You were awful to me. And you're killing the company!
我没想过那些事。
I didn't think about those things.
我的意思是,可怕!
I mean, awful!
毯子里的猪?
Pig in a blanket?
特洛伊，你是个很棒的程序员。
Troy, you're an amazing coder.
Jackhouse !
Jackhouse!
我可能因为一些私人问题
I may have let some personal issues
云我的判断。
cloud my judgment.
视频游戏。那是我一直以来想做的
Video games. That's all I've ever wanted to do
我的全部…
my entire...
我的整个生活。
my entire life.
制作电子游戏，你知道吗?
Make video games, you know?
使只是…一个伟大的比赛。
Make just... one great game.
相同。
Same.
是的…
Yeah...
嗯…我得回去工作了。
Well... I better get back to work.
你是对的。你应该。
You're right. You should.
我们运气真好。
We lucked out.
我们在那封邮件毁掉代码之前拿到了一份。
We secured a copy of the code before that email destroyed it.
但是，我们需要你。
But, we need you.
等等，所以你还有机会在Pixelcon发布游戏?
Wait, so you still have a chance to launch at Pixelcon?
是的，我想是的。
Yeah, I think so.
如果你能回来帮忙的话。
If you'll come back and help.
吉米，你到底在干什么?
Jimmy, what the hell are you doing?
爸，抱歉，你还记得我以前的老板，特洛伊·梅菲尔德吗?
Dad, sorry, um, you remember my old boss, Troy Mayfield?
《歌舞青春》。怎么样，伙计?
Hey, High School Musical. How's it hanging, buddy?
我是唯一可以这么叫他的人。
Hey, I'm the only one allowed to call him that.
至少他还是个孩子。
At least he's a kid.
他要玩电子游戏。
He's expected to play video games.
让视频游戏!
Make video games!
你得回去工作了。
You need to get back to work.
爸爸,你是对的。
You're right, Dad.
我做的事。
I do.
听着，我很不擅长卖房地产。
Look, I am actively terrible at selling real estate.
视频游戏设计,
Video game design,
那是我这辈子最想做的事。
that's all I've ever wanted to do with my life.
显然，我很擅长这个。
And apparently, I'm pretty good at it.
你去把这些零食拿给那些买家
You go and you take these snacks to those buyers
否则我就不再帮你了
or I'm not gonna help you out anymore.
没关系,爸爸。谢谢你！
It's okay, Dad. Thank you.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
那不是吉米。他没有发邮件。
It wasn't Jimmy. He didn't send the email.
嘿，我可以为我自己说话。
Hey, I can speak for myself.
这不是我。我没有发那封邮件。
It wasn't me. I didn't send the email.
就我而言，我从未怀疑过你。
I, for one, never doubted you.
我百分之百地怀疑你。
I doubted you one hundred percent.
电子邮件是什么?
What's an email?
女士们。先生们。
Ladies. Gentlemen.
我们失去了很多时间。
We've lost a lot of time.
好吧，那就不能浪费时间了。
Well, then, there's no time to lose.
我们能帮上什么忙?
How can we help?
我们叫了援军!
We called in some reinforcements!
你有什么主意，特洛伊?
What's your idea, Troy?
你们觉得我们该怎么办?
What do you guys think we should do?
你问我们?
You're asking us?
是啊，我们都是操场游戏，对吧?
Yeah, we're all Playfield Games, right?
佐伊，比利，甚至迪尔先生。
Zoey, Billy, even Mr. Diehl.
我想听你们大声说出来。
So, I want to hear you guys speak up.
是时候听了。
It's just time that I listen.
我们没法和Xodus竞争
Well, we can't compete with Xodus
图像和声音。
on graphics and sound.
我们需要找到真正的玩家真正想玩的东西。
We need to find something that real gamers really want to play.
我在想……
I was thinking...
算了吧。
Forget it.
不，玛丽，怎么了?
No, Marie, what's up?
如果我们那样做呢?
What if we did that?
做什么?
Did what?
我们让球员打球……
We get the players to play...
和…与我们的代码。
and... code with us.
所以，我们给了他们构建游戏世界的工具，
So, we give them the tools to build the world of the game,
然后，构建世界就变成了游戏。
and then, building the world becomes the game.
好吧。好吧,你想……
All right. Well, you want...
．..你想让他们这么做，对吧?
...you want to get them to do this, right?
但是我们要怎么做呢
But how are we going to do that
如果这些玩家从未见过一行代码，
if these gamers have never even seen a line of code,
不要介意写一个?
never mind written one?
吉米，你给杰克豪斯的地图编辑
Uh, actually, Jimmy, your map editor for Jackhouse
是很强大的…
is pretty powerful...
对，对，对，梅菲尔德。
Right, right, right, Mayfield.
是的。
Yeah.
所以，我们将编辑器包含在游戏的可执行文件中。
So, we include the editor in the executable of the game.
我喜欢这个!
I love this!
我明白了。
I get it.
我们使用你说的现有架构…
We use the existing architecture like you said...
——啊。-然后…
- Ah. - But then...
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
♪嘿♪
♪ Hey ♪
>给我
♪ Give it to me ♪
是的,谢谢。
Yeah, thanks.
是的，这些看起来都很好。
Yeah, so, this all looks good.
-是的。——给我。
- Yeah. - Show me.
是的,好的。
Yeah, okay.
嘿,妈妈。妈妈,你在这里。
Hey, Mom. Mom, you're here.
嘿。
Hey.
医生给我开了绿灯。
My doctor gave me the green light.
但你是好吗?你明白吗?
But you're good? You're okay?
是的。亲爱的，怎么了?
Yeah. Honey, what's going on?
说来话长。
It's a long story.
我们不打算展示杰克豪斯或尤特。
We're actually not going to demo Jackhouse or Yort.
我们结合了两场比赛中最好的部分，
We married the best parts of both games,
所以现在我们叫它。
and so now we're calling it...
头脑风暴!
Brainstorm!
我知道怎么用吉米的地图了。
I figured out how to use Jimmy's maps.
他们与头脑风暴完美配合。
They work perfectly with Brainstorm.
这是唯一一个把开源编码变成游戏的游戏
It's the only game that turns open source coding
真正的游戏体验。
into the actual gaming experience.
是啊，还有全世界的人
Yeah, and everyone in the world
可以一起玩头脑风暴，这很酷。
can play Brainstorm together, it's pretty cool.
这是你爸爸的旧文件夹吗?
Is this one of your dad's old binders?
是的。
Yeah.
你在哪里找到的?
Where did you find it?
就在我最需要他的时候出现了。
It just kind of showed up when I needed him most.
我爱它。
I love it.
这就是Playfield的意义所在。
This is what Playfield is all about.
我为你们感到骄傲。但是，我必须说实话。
I'm very proud of you guys. But, I have to be honest.
如果这个游戏没有进展，
If this game doesn't really move,
然后我们要卖掉公司……
then we've got to sell the company...
或者关闭它。
or shut it down.
我们知道。林登不能保守秘密。
We know. Lyndon can't keep a secret.
哦……嗯…呃……
Errr... uh... errrr...
好吧。嗯，你认为
Okay. Well, do you think
这个游戏真的值得冒这个险吗?
that this game is really worth risking it all?
——地狱,是的。——是的!
- Hell, yeah. - Yeah!
我不是为Xodus工作的。
Well, I'm not working for Xodus.
吉米?
Jimmy?
我想是的。
I think it is.
好吧。
Okay.
我相信我的家人从来没有错。
I have never gone wrong by trusting my family.
所以，让我们向世界展示我们的能力。
So, let's show the world what we can do.
好了，我们走吧!
All right, let's go!
头脑风暴衬衫为每个人!
Brainstorm shirts for everyone!
吉米，这到底是怎么回事?
Jimmy, what's this game all about, anyway?
我们将在前往Pixelcon的路上向你展示更多内容。
We'll show you more on the way to Pixelcon.
但是，你会喜欢的。
But, you're going to love it.
好吧。
Okay.
>跟我说话
♪ Talk to me ♪
♬我在外面等车…♪我> < /
♪ I'm waiting For a ride outside... ♪
——嘿,家伙。我MatPat…… - ♬Talk to me♬
- Hey, guys. I'm MatPat... - ♪ Talk to me ♪
…在今年的Pixelcon上为您直播
...broadcasting to you live from this year's Pixelcon.
i am pumped for Xodus' s new title
I am pumped for Xodus' new title...
>你就像我的糖
♪ Need you now You're like sugar to me ♪
♬你就像我的糖
♪ You're like sugar to me ♪
我现在需要你
♪ I need you now ♪
．..所以我说，你现在被解雇了。
...so I was like, you're fired right now.
-我喜欢。-滚出去
- I love that. - Get out of here
-不然我就报警!-太棒了。
- before I call the cops! - That's so brilliant.
我是说，它很旧了。
I mean, it's old.
-他们在这里做什么?-不知道，长官
- What are they doing here? - No idea, sir.
好吧，笑吧
All right, just-just laugh
好像我说了些很好笑的话。
like I said something really funny.
——好的。-是的。
- Okay. - Yeah.
对不起,。我很抱歉。
Sorry,. I'm sorry.
——对不起。- 你会活下来吗?
- Sorry. - Will you survive?
不,绝对不是。
No, absolutely not.
Planet Hell, Alien Reaper.
哇。
Wow.
孩子们，你们准备好再偷你妈妈的信用卡了吗?
Kids, are you ready to steal your mom's credit card again?
特洛伊，快过来!
Troy, get over here!
我无法让演示程序启动。
I can't get the demo to boot up.
今天早上起作用了。
It worked this morning.
——什么?怎么了?——不知道。
- What? What's wrong? - No idea.
我试着一切。我不能连接!
I've tried everything. I can't connect!
你们觉得我们该怎么办?
What do you guys think we should do?
修好它，特洛伊!
Just fix it, Troy!
没事的,来吧。
It's okay, c'mon.
Xodus永远!
Xodus forever!
Xodus糟透了!
Xodus sucks!
谁说的?
Who said that?
你知道是谁说的吗?
Can you figure out who said that?
。谢谢你,Xodus。
All right. Thank you, Xodus.
对于我们的最终演示，
For our final presentation,
下面有请Playfield Games!
next up, please welcome Playfield Games!
伙计们，我们没时间了!
Guys, we don't have any more time!
——继续努力。-真遗憾
- Keep trying. - It's a real shame
你不可能打败我们的小样。
you're not going to be able to beat our demo.
这是一件很疯狂的事情
It is such a crazy thing
你的游戏机现在不能用了。
that your console's not working right now.
Playfield，你有60秒展示你的游戏
Playfield, you have 60 seconds to present your game
or you will没收你的演讲场地
or you will forfeit your presentation spot.
哦，这太粗糙了。坏运气。
Ooh, that is rough. Tough luck there.
怎么这么久?
What is taking so long?
他们无法让游戏发挥作用。
They can't get the game to work.
进入城市
♪ Step into the city ♪
通过游戏构建它
♪ Build it through the game ♪
新的生活在等待着你永远不要重蹈覆辙
♪ A new life awaits you Never be the same ♪
欢迎来到你的命运，在那里事情开始改变
♪ Welcome to your destiny Where things start to change ♪
加入你的朋友♬
♪ Join up with your friends ♪
我是头脑的头脑风暴
♪ I'm the brainstorm Of the brain ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
♬感受雷声
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
-你的IP地址是什么?- ♬头脑风暴♬ .♬
- What's your IP address? - ♪ Brainstorm ♪
这不是工作。
It's not working.
这是接受我提议的最后机会了，凯特。
Last chance to take my offer, Kate.
在这种情况下，我会说
And under the circumstances, I would say
这是你最好的选择。
this is your best possible option.
看看他拿的是什么。
Look at what he's holding.
♬感受雷声
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
头脑风暴是一个奇迹
♪ Brainstorm it's a wonder ♪
好了，伙计们，别在这里疯了。
Okay, guys, let's not get crazy here.
这是个信号干扰器。
It's a signal jammer.
该死的,林登!
Damn, Lyndon!
吉米，现在试试!
Jimmy, try it now!
- 头脑风暴 -我是赤手空拳冠军
- ♪ Brainstorm ♪ - I was a bare-knuckle champion
就在战后。
right after the war.
什么战争?
What war?
这是一个奇迹
♪ It's a wonder ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
♬感受雷声
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
是的!
Yes!
头脑风暴。
Brainstorm.
可以吗，梅菲尔德夫人?
Was that okay, Mrs. Mayfield?
这是惊人的。
That was amazing.
——谢谢。——谢谢!
- Thank you. - Thank you!
我的腿没知觉了。
I can't feel my legs.
哇。你好,Pixelcon !
Wow. Hello, Pixelcon!
我是Kate Mayfield, Playfield Games的首席执行官。
I'm Kate Mayfield, CEO of Playfield Games.
这是我们最新游戏《头脑风暴》的主题曲。
That was the theme song for our latest game, Brainstorm!
现在我想请出我们的首席设计师…
So now, I would like to bring out our lead designer...
——这就是你。——这就是你。
- That's you. - That's you.
我们的首席设计师。
Well, our lead designers.
让他们给你演示一下。
And have them walk you through the demo.
请欢迎吉米·蒂斯代尔和特洛伊·梅菲尔德。
Please welcome Jimmy Tisdale and Troy Mayfield.
嘿,每一个人。
Hey, everybody.
整个世界和游戏玩法
This entire world and the gameplay
旨在鼓励团队合作……
has been designed to encourage teamwork...
给您前所未有的访问我们的内容创建工具。
giving you unprecedented access to our content creation tools.
实际上……我们要把大家都叫来吗?
Actually... should we call everyone up?
让我们做它。
Let's do it.
抱歉，我能请到整个团队吗
Uh, sorry, if I could just get the entire team
请出来。
to come out, please.
嘿，伙计们，你们能出来一下吗?
Hey guys, can you come out here?
劳拉、玛丽、林登…
Laura, Marie, Lyndon...
来吧,林登。
Come on, Lyndon.
我们的团队。
Our team.
老实说，我们不知道这场游戏会如何收场。
To be honest, we don't know how this game ends.
我们把这个问题留给你，因为实际上，
We're leaving that up to you because in effect,
是你，玩家，创造了游戏。
it's you, the players, who make the game.
玛丽吗?
Marie?
你迈出的每一步都揭示了一个新的世界。
Every step you take reveals a new part of the world.
我们在操场制造零件
Parts we make at Playfield
还有你和其他玩家制造的零件。
and parts you and all the other players make.
每一个加入的玩家都能帮助你看到更多
Every player that joins helps you see even more
并在游戏中添加自己独特的元素。
and adds their own unique touches to the game.
我们的游戏就像生活。
Our game is like life.
你可以选择独自思考或者…
You can choose to brainstorm alone or...
哦!嗯…
Oh! Um...
或者获得更多乐趣并创造出更好的游戏
or have more fun and make a better game
和你的朋友和家人一起工作。
working with your friends and your family.
是啊，你们在一起玩的越多
Yeah, the more you play together in the world
去探索，你能改变的就越多。
and explore, the more you can change it.
很酷,对吧?
Pretty cool, right?
对吧?
Right?
特洛伊，你有什么要说的吗?
Uh, Troy, anything you'd like to say?
已经超过5万了!
That's like over 50,000 already!
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh !
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhh!
在线结果在
The online results are in
最好的新游戏演示是……
and the best new game demo is...
球场比赛“头脑风暴!
Playfield Games' Brainstorm!
球场的游戏规则!
Playfield Games rules!
噢!噢!
Ow! Ow!
球场规则!
Playfield rules!
今天真是美好的一天。
This has been a pretty good day.
This has been a great day.
我只希望你父亲能在这里看到。
I only wish your father could be here to see it.
他是。
He is.
嘿。
Hey.
爸爸，这个游戏太棒了!
Daddy, this game is awesome!
你做这个吗?
You made this?
好吧，我们一起做了。
Well, together, we all did.
真的吗?
Really?
嗯。
Hmm.
好东西。
Good stuff.
嘿,爸爸?
Hey, Dad?
是吗?
Yeah?
待会一起吃晚饭好吗，就我们三个?
Want to get dinner later, just the three of us?
是的,好的。你买。
Yeah, okay. You're buying.
好吧。
Okay.
我也想要一件那种t恤。
And I want one of those T-shirts.
嘿，你做到了!
Hey, you did it!
你做到了。这一切都是你做的。
You did it. You did all of this.
你真了不起。
You're amazing.
我们所做的。我们是了不起的。
We did. We're amazing.
这一切感觉就像个美梦。
This all just kinda feels like a good dream.
这不是梦。
It's not a dream.
Whoo-hoo !特洛伊艾克曼,MVP !
Whoo-hoo! Troy Aikman, MVP!
啊,吉米?
Ah, Jimmy?
哦……
Oh...
好吧……对吧……嗯…
Okay... right... um...
一垒。
First base.
球场回来了。
Playfield is back.
老实说,图形,故事…
Honestly, the graphics, the story...
字面上从来没有更兴奋
Literally have never been more excited
关于一个游戏在我的生活中发行
about a game release in my life...
有时一个游戏出现在
Sometimes a game comes along
，你只是不知道期望什么
that you have just no idea what to expect
，这就是这个游戏
and that's what this game is...
预购，注册我!
Pre-order, sign me up!
那么，头脑风暴的续集怎么样了?
So, how's the Brainstorm sequel coming?
伙计，你会抓狂的。
Dude, you're gonna freak.
你要拍下这个过程吗?
Hey, you gonna film this session?
-可能会很好。——你好,尼克。
- It might be pretty good. - Hi, Nick.
我要拍吗?
Am I gonna film?
伙计，课后编程是我最受欢迎的内容!
Dude, afterschool coding is my most popular content!
对吧?
Right?
嘿，怎么了，伙计?
Hey, what's up, man?
把这个。是的。喜欢它吗?
Put this on. Yeah. Like it?
是的。看看这个。你看起来不错，伙计。
Yeah. Look at that. You look good, man.
好吧。
All right.
你好,昵称!
Hello, Nicknames!
欢迎来到返校编程的另一集
Welcome to another episode of back to school coding
他就是特洛伊·梅菲尔德
with the man himself, Troy Mayfield.
-好，大家好。新商品刚刚投放…
- All right, hello, everyone. - New merch just dropped...
-有空就去看看。-今天，我想给你看看
- just check it out when you can. - Today, I want to show you
这是我们刚在Playfield安装的
something we just installed at Playfield
-下面的链接。-…我喜欢叫它
- Link down below. - ...that I like to call
团队的梦想家。
Team Dreamer.
它是一个需要每个人的组模块
It is a group module that requires every person
至少写一行代码
to write at least one line of code
所以每个人都在为游戏做出贡献。
so everyone is contributing to the game.
你们在看什么?
What are you guys looking at?
哇,这是……
Whoa, this is...
伙计，这些图像太疯狂了。
Dude, these graphics are insane.
艾米丽?你在这里干什么?
Emily? Wh-What are you doing here?
我爸爸说我也许可以
My dad said I might be able to
向你学习。
learn something from you.
好吧。
Okay.
这游戏是你自己做的吗?
Um, did you make this game all by yourself?
它还没有完全完成。
It's not quite finished yet.
伙计，这可能是头脑风暴的好机会。
Dude, this could be Brainstorm good.
她可能比你强……
She might be better than you...
各位，把艾米丽的游戏载入梦想之队
Well everyone, let's load Emily's game into Team Dreamer
看看会发生什么。
and see what happens.
艾米丽，为什么不让我们进去?
Emily, wh-why don't you let us in?
我不需要任何帮助。
I don't need any help.
嘿,他们……
Hey, Em...
你越打开这些，
You know, the more you open these,
你能做得越好。
the better you can make this.
相信我吗?
Trust me?
好吧。大家都来吧。
All right. Have at it, everyone.
让我们一起看看能做些什么。
Let's see what we can do together.
我爸爸在他的活页夹里写道
My dad wrote in his binder,
"千万不要跳过过场动画
"Never skip the cut scenes.
完成所有的任务。
Complete all the quests.
和玩多人游戏的每一个机会，你得到。"
And play multi-player every chance you get."
如果你真的想打败游戏，
Oh, and if you really want to beat the game,
总是让坏人知道谁是老大
always show the bad guy who's boss.
第二位。
Second place.
更像是第一个失败者。
More like first loser.
梅菲尔德吗?
Mayfield?
这孩子到底想要什么?
What the hell does this kid want?
“你是霍格沃茨的哪个学院?”
"Which Hogwarts house are you?"
这是个好问题。
Well, that's a good question.
嗯?
Huh?
是的。
Yeah.
赫奇帕奇?
Hufflepuff?
没有办法。
There's no way.
哦,什么?
Uh, what?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
电脑都烧坏了。这是谁干的?
The computers are fried. Who the hell did this?
特洛伊!
Troy!
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
Feel the thunder♬
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
这是一个奇迹
♪ It's a wonder ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
Feel the thunder♬
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
Run into the darkness我们都知道它被制造出来了
♪ Run into the darkness We all know it's made ♪
>准备点燃你的大脑皮层静脉
♪ Ready to ignite Your cerebral cortex vein ♪
成为我的门徒被困在我的域里
♪ Become my disciple Trapped in my domain ♪
♬你永远不会打败我
♪ You will never beat me ♪
♬我是头脑风暴
♪ I'm the brainstorm Of the brain ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
Feel the thunder♬
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
♬头脑风暴，这是一个奇迹
♪ Brainstorm, it's a wonder ♪
♪♪头脑风暴
♪ Brainstorm ♪
Feel the thunder♬
♪ Feel the thunder ♪
♬从我八岁开始♬
♪ Ever since I was eight years old ♪
我知道我想成为什么
♪ I knew what I wanted to be ♪
>   >
♪ Ever since I had A thought in my head ♪
♬只是专注于我能看到的♬
♪ Just focused on What I could see ♪
>当我还是个小男孩的时候
♪ Ever since I was a young boy ♪
我曾是一个有伟大梦想的男孩
♪ I was a boy With mighty big dreams ♪
>当我还是个小男孩的时候
♪ Ever since I was a young boy ♪
我曾是一个有伟大梦想的男孩
♪ I was a boy With mighty big dreams ♪
Hello to my future self  Hello to my past
♪ Hello to my future self Hello to my past ♪
不知道这是什么感觉
♪ Don't know what this feeling is ♪
我希望它能持续
♪ I hope it's gonna last ♪
♬我不能做的一件事是跟踪时间
♪ One thing that I can't do Is keep track of time ♪
我忙着不让自己失去理智…♪♪
♪ I'm too busy trying Not to lose my mind... ♪♪